Want to be a pro player?
A new journey
is about to begin.
The door to going pro
is now open to you.
So?
Are you ready?
Embark on the journey.
Reach the very top
and feel the glory of the summit.
To climb up,
you don’t have to be a veteran.
Past failures
shouldn’t stop you from trying again.
Even if it’s your first time,
every dream is possible.
Glory’s Challengers League season
is about to begin.
The glorious crown
awaits you.
Hey, Ms. Chen.
I was gonna ask you to play with me,
but I heard you made your own team?
Yeah.
[157 days until Challengers League
registration. Let’s do our best!]
Based on the top-eight ranking
as the regular season ended last month,
the former powerhouse Excellent Era
has been eliminated.
It’s a big upset indeed.
Let’s check in with Excellent Era
and see what they have to say.
After the relegation,
will your roster see any changes?
I’ll stay with Excellent Era
as we endure this difficult time.
In next season’s Challengers,
I will lead Excellent Era
back onto this stage.
Our team is
in an unprecedented predicament.
We’ve tried to contact
the retired former captain,
Ye Qiu.
We had hoped Ye Qiu
could act as a consultant
and help Excellent Era
identify the cause of our failures.
Unfortunately,
all our efforts to reach Ye Qiu
were met with flat refusal.
We’ll do our best to make up
Incredible!
They’re the ones who threw you out!
for the gap that he left behind.
They make it sound like you abandoned them!
Excellent Era will approach the next round
with a stronger lineup.
Please accompany us on this journey.
[Excellent Era is the only team for me,
I’ve never heard of the other teams!]
[Ye Qiu is such a traitor!]
They’re looking good.
They’re plenty good.
But we’re doomed!
Look at the news.
Excellent Era’s dropped
to the Challengers League.
When you called me
and said you’d form a team,
it sounded great.
[Player: Wei Chen, Happy.Windward
Formation, Job: Warlock]
Well?
[Player: Ye Xiu, Happy.Lord Grim,
Job: Unspecialized]
Want a ride, buddy?
What?
You wanna be champion?
Could anything else be as fun?
[Challengers League]
And now?
We must face Excellent Era
in the Challengers League!
What do we do now?
Champion?
We might not qualify at all!
Who could’ve thought?
They’re so bad they got relegated!
You haven’t been yourself lately.
Are you worried about this?
Of course I am!
It’s Excellent Era!
Just look at character stats,
never mind player skills.
Their characters’ offensive stats
are way better than ours!
That’s true.
Excellent Era is a luxurious team.
Their players and accounts are
all top-tier.
They even have One Autumn Leaf,
also known as Battle God.
God-level characters like this
have their whole bodies
covered with silver weapons.
As for us,
we only have two silver weapons.
But we still have you, Ye Xiu.
And Mumu!
[Ally]
Su Mucheng?
Your best partner?
Will she join us?
She has to wait until next season.
[Ally]
[Enemy]
No!
We have no chance of winning at all.
I’m going to retire on the spot.
Is Excellent Era that good?
Didn’t they get one of the lowest scores
this season?
They should be pretty noob, right?
What terrible teammates.
Although Mucheng can’t join us,
our equipment
is also indeed much weaker,
we have our strengths.
Don’t we still have you?
Former captain of Team Blue Rain,
Wei Chen the Great.
Although you were defeated miserably
by Excellent Era back then,
your league-famous dirty playstyle
is so obscene that even now
it’s unmatched in the league.
Dealing with the young players
of Excellent Era,
you are our hidden weapon.
I see.
That’s true.
Seriously?
I believe
Happy will be very different
in the future.
Very different!
As for money and materials?
We’ll figure it out soon.
Don’t you have
an exclusive secret method
to get skill points?
I spent several years working on it.
What do you want?
Gaining skill points?
Can’t you get it
from doing ordinary missions?
One Autumn Leaf’s skill points,
if I remember correctly,
it’s 4840.
What a huge difference.
I think Soft Mist
only has 720.
Can we buy it?
Skill points can only be obtained
through missions and game events.
It’s very random.
Although it is so difficult
to obtain them,
a normal pro player character
generally has above 4700 points.
Thus,
[Skill point improvement]
if we can improve our skill points,
we can grow our character quickly.
That’s right.
Wow.
I can’t believe you found
such a great method.
Are you looking down on me?
Do you know how many skill points
Windward Formation has?
How many?
The character with the highest
skill points in Glory currently
is Desert Dust, right?
4880.
So,
how about yours?
Just say it already.
What about my Windward Formation?
It’s nothing much.
A mere 4920.
Wouldn’t that make you
the character with
the most skill points in Glory?
So-so.
But this is just an empirical theory.
Windward Formation took a long time
to succeed.
It’s still far from ready
for mass production.
That’s why
I have already hired a professional
to research it.
How many solutions has he shown?
This seems to be
the fifth one.
I didn’t even understand the question.
I can’t copy anymore.
That’s insane.
When will it end?
Will it ever end?
[Lord Grim]
Did the bell ring already?
The thing I sent you last time,
how’s the research going?
Am I hallucinating?
Concealed Light replied to me.
Ask about the situation quickly.
Just video call him.
Can you see me?
Wow, there’s so many of you.
Hey, Concealed Light.
The thing I sent you the last time,
have you deciphered it yet?
The information you gave me,
I studied it carefully.
I calculated the data
and found many possibilities.
Then, through inverse reasoning,
I corrected some data errors.
Based on all the data and calculations,
I built a final mathematical model.
What on earth?
Concealed Light,
do you think
we can understand this?
Don’t you understand at all?
I really can’t wrap my head around it.
Can you use the language you use
when writing guides
to describe what we should do?
I got you.
Wait a minute.
Thanks for your hard work.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Very good.
The guide is very detailed.
So complicated.
Other than the Realm of Gods,
District 10
also has many tasks.
Yeah.
Let’s start with District 10.
[Your friend, Lord Grim is online]
Attention everybody.
The devil Lord Grim is back.
Everyone, please keep
a close eye on him!
[Isn’t that Lord Grim?]
[Why is he in the common area?]
[Why is he back?]
[What is he up to this time?]
This operation is very important.
We only have one shot at every mission.
If we make a mistake,
there will be no chance
of obtaining the skill book reward
for this mission.
Obtaining the skill book depends
on probability, to begin with.
So
cherish every mission opportunity.
Be sure to follow the order
of the guide.
That’s weird.
They’re really just completing missions.
Yeah.
[Mission List]
[Mission completed!]
You didn’t get it either?
I got it!
What?
The boss lady got it.
What do you mean?
Aren’t you too worried?
How can I not worry?
It’s Excellent Era we’re talking about.
Yes.
It’s just Excellent Era.
Haven’t you seen them?
I’ve seen them.
The Excellent Era back then
was even more glorious than it is now.
In comparison,
I’ve changed even more
than me back then.
What’s wrong with you now?
You have advantages
you didn’t have back then.
Like what? Age?
That’s one of them.
Is there anything else?
The guy who led Excellent Era
and beat you
is your teammate now.
That’s what I’m worried about.
[Excellent Era]
I’ve never viewed Excellent Era
this way before.
Which way?
Excellent Era!
Ye.
Captain.
I did well this time, right?
We are three-peat champions!
I now see them as
a target that must be defeated.
That’s right.
No matter what tricks
Excellent Era will use,
we must defeat them!
[Skill Points: 4970, Player: Tang Rou
Happy.Soft Mist, Job: Battle Mage]
It’s out!
[Skill Points: 4930, Player: Bao Rongxing
Happy.Steamed Bun Invasion, Job: Brawler]
Wow!
[Skill Points: 5000, Player: Ye Xiu
Happy.Lord Grim, Job: Unspecialized]
Awesome!
That’s higher than mine!
[Skill Points: 4800, Player: Chen Guo
Happy.Chasing Haze, Job: Launcher]
Glory has been around for 10 years.
[Skill Points: 4170, Player: An Wenyi
Happy·Little Cold Hands, Job: Cleric]
There has never been a character
with more than 5000 skill points.
Even after studying it for many years,
Wei Chen wasn’t able
to repeat the results consistently.
It’s all thanks to you,
Concealed Light.
Actually, I only did some of the work.
It was mostly thanks to my mentor,
Dr. Zhang.
Why did you get your mentor
involved in this?
What’s the use of you asking this?
What do you know about university?
Haven’t you heard of that saying?
Even if I haven’t eaten pork,
I have seen pigs running.
You saw pigs running in a university?
I can’t communicate
with an uncultured person like you.
Concealed Light.
Who are you exactly?
Do you want to see my CV?
Let me see.
[Document from Luo Ji,
"National Scholarship Application Form"]
Enrolled at the age of 17
through the Special Talent Program.
Direct PhD in Mathematics.
What?
What does that mean?
I have never heard of that.
That means I continued my PhD studies
right after my undergraduate course.
There is a traitor among us!
[Qingming]
[Nanshan Cemetery]
I’m going over here.
What about you two?
Our spot is further away
ahead.
I’ll see you guys later then.
Okay.
See you then.
See you later.
I wonder
who they are going to visit together.
[Beloved Brother]
Muqiu.
We’re here to visit you.
[Beloved Brother, Su Muqiu]
You’re a pretty awesome, new kid.
Su Muqiu.
You’re crap today.
It seems like you met
your opponent today.
Su Muqiu.
Come back when you’re full.
Are you guys done yet?
[Excellent Era Cybercafe]
Hey.
Do you have nowhere to go?
Do you want to come to our house?
There are only two in our family.
It’s three.
Don’t forget the cat!
Ye Qiu.
Have you ever thought about going pro?
Pro?
Seems good.
Why did you dismantle
my equipment again?
I will give you a better one later.
Are you going to cry again
the next time I beat you?
Who cried?
Our records are almost equal, okay?
If you don’t believe me, ask Mucheng.
Okay, maybe you have a small advantage.
If there is a weapon
that can match different jobs
and transform into various weapon forms,
it must be very cool.
A special weapon
for Unspecialized characters.
What a genius idea.
I want to explore
more possibilities in Glory.
Sure.
Anyway, there will be plenty of time
in the future.
After the release of Awakening Missions
at level 55 for every job,
the era of the Unspecialized is over.
The idea of
the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella failed.
This is for you, as a souvenir.
Are you okay?
It’s nothing.
I’ll just start all over again.
Haven’t I told you before?
Unspecialized can go through
the Realm of Gods challenge
and continue to level up.
After a long journey,
we’re back to square one.
I think it’s a good time
to bring back a new possibility
like the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella
and scare the guys in the Alliance.
The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella
was his work?
Did your brother make it?
Yeah.
If he weren’t resting here,
now
he must be one
of the top players of Glory.
At that time, he was about
to sign a formal contract with the team.
Then, the accident happened.
But he still left a lot of things behind.
That’s right.
One Autumn Leaf’s spear,
Evil Annihilation
is his handiwork.
How brilliant.
Oh, right.
There’s Lord Grim
and the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella.
Those are all the things he left behind.
There’s also my Dancing Rain.
Muqiu ever wanted to use it to go pro.
We must get into
the professional league.
And win the championship.
Of course.
[Next episode preview]
The characters from Samsara
suddenly seem much stronger
than during the regular season.
Over all these years, thanks to
the support of my team, my teammates,
and many Glory players.
What a pity.
What Xiao Shiqin is best at
is using his enemy's information
to develop meticulous
tactical arrangements.
He must have not expected the changes
from Samsara.
It's 1 versus 3!
Does Huang Shaotian intend to lower
the health of three opponents by himself?