This is game
1 of the 8th
Grand Finals of Glory,
All in the world shall be reborn
samsara champ!
samsara goat!
Samsara the champion!
Samsara champion!!
samsara da goat!
Zhou Zekai the GOAT!
Samsara champs!
and Samsara
SAMSARA!
Zhou Zekai is my daddy!
gun king da boss!
samsara champion!
peak enjoyment!
have just won their home match.
Gun King = boss!
I always believe that Samsara will win, no matter who the opponent is!
Dear Zhou, I love you!
Samsara is the champion!!
I cried. Has Samsara reached the end?
.
# Team Samsara places first! #
Summary: Samsara wins 1st round of Glory Playoffs!
All
Hot
Recent
After one round,
Samsara leads Blue Rain with a score
of 7.5 to 2.
What?
Samsara is so lucky.
They must have prayed to God.
Bug.
What a bad sport!
So annoying!
Worm.
They are so unsophisticated.
They only won once, but they act
as if they are the champions.
I dare you
to a one-on-one challenge in the arena.
Samsara’s so arrogant!
You’re just jealous!
Blue Rain is the champ!!
!Hoo boy, they’re mad!
Kids, go finish your homework!
I never liked Samsara!
You guys are ridiculous!
Blue Rain fans, stop showing off!
With an attitude like that, you
Blue Rain fans can just uninstall!
Samsara sure likes to put on airs!
I just love how you hate us
but can’t do anything!
Chasing Haze
Player: Chen Guo
Class: Launcher
Happy
They’re even fighting over it
[Player: Tang Rou. Happy.Soft Mist.]
[Job: Battle Mage.]
[Player: Bao Rongxin.]
[Happy.Steamed Bun Invasion. Job: Brawler.]
in the public game now.
We have a boss!
The Dark Light of the Dark Temple has been updated.
[Chatting with Loulan Slash]
Guys!
Well done getting it
right as the match ended.
It appeared earlier,
[Player: Lou Guanning. Heavenly Justice.]
[Loulan Slash. Job: Berserker.]
but the match was so intense
[Chatting with Lord Grim]
I forgot to watch my game.
You even offered to team up and split the boss
materials in half. I’m really sorry.
Now, all the guilds are here.
Blue Brook Guild, too.
I’m really sorry.
How’s the boss?
It’s still alive.
Blue Brook is going first!
[Player: Xu Boyuan. Blue Brook Guild.]
Knight, draw the aggro.
Blue Bridge Spring Snow
[Blue Bridge Spring Snow. Job: Blade Master]
Mage, keep attacking.
Reinforcements are coming.
That’s finalists for you.
Come on,
let’s join them.
Off to the Dark Temple we go!
TRAIN ZONE
Let’s go.
Captain’s group is attacking.
Aren’t we
going inside?
Let’s deal with Blue Brook’s reinforcements
while we’re here.
WWang：野怪刷经验组我++++++++
琴音飘渺：勇者无畏公会诚邀各位有志之士加入！我们公会氛围融洽，
活动丰富，一起征服这个世界吧！
绕岸垂杨　死亡
［地图］［羽化］：刚从南边儿回来，那里真是值得打卡一去！
雷鸣电光　死亡
幻梦影：请问哪里可以捕捉到珍稀的材料？
云归　死亡
知月倾城　死亡
曙光旋冰　死亡
＜·系统公告＞　每日日常活动己经开启，各位玩家可前往活动区域接取
任务。
绕岸垂杨　死亡
What’s going on?
Our reinforcements were eliminated?
Lord Grim?
Why are you here?
God Ye!
You’re finally here.
Do we attack the team or the boss?
Let’s do both at once.
Come on.
Let’s reorganize.
Split by class.
Go!
Bao, Tang Rou.
Kill the Cleric.
Heavenly Justice, aggro the boss.
Bao, come with me.
Buddy.
You’re too much, snatching the boss like this.
Less talking.
Go get the boss now.
Isn’t that his account?
How is Blue River doing recently?
I am Blue River.
It’s you?
You’ve returned to the Realm of Gods.
You know who I am, then.
Are you here
to get beaten up?
Don’t you run away!
Run?
This is a tactic, buddy.
If you don’t get it, please keep quiet.
You’re still coming after me?
The boss is ours now.
Take your men and leave.
Lord Grim.
Stop!
He’s so weak.
Bao.
Don’t mind him.
Come with me.
Did you hear me?
Be grateful when I’m still nice to you.
Gosh.
Stop them.
If you want to die,
I can’t do anything about it.
He’s too pathetic.
Since when are you so shameless?
Enough is enough.
Shameless?
What’s that comment?
I attack you
based on my clear and right judgment.
Now, everyone is fighting for the boss.
You mess up the entire game.
Why am I shameless?
[Waiting for respawn. Do you want to]
[respawn at the city? Yes/No]
How would I dare to attack you alone?
Was I really looking for trouble?
What are the reward items?
Great.
There are a few materials.
[Player: Mo Fan. Deception. Job: Ninja]
The guild leader is ousted.
His materials are taken away!
It’s Deception!
That guy…
He’s a scavenger who always
raids and robs others.
Deception?
Bao.
No wonder he’s so creepy.
Hurry up and guard the door.
I’m telling you
to guard the door in the game.
This is definitely our weak point.
Disperse and search for it.
If he’s alone, it’d be great
if we can lure him.
Over here.
If the battle is over, he’ll sign out.
If we’re unable
to locate him for a long while,
it’d be hard for us
Stop!
to locate him again.
His job is Ninja.
His name is Deception.
Specialized in scavenging.
Characteristic, sleazy.
Very sleazy.
He’s quite good.
Don’t you run!
Bao.
Tang.
All you think is to avoid me.
You don’t even bother about us.
You can’t run now.
Give us the item.
Just run.
Why aren’t you running away?
I dare you to run now.
You’re skillful.
Can we be friends?
I’m establishing a team now.
We need more members.
If you’re willing to join us,
you can keep
what you took.
Consider it as a gift from me.
Buddy.
He’s not your buddy.
He’s offline now.
Kill him.
There are three materials
from the LV70 over-world boss.
Yet, we got none of it from him.
However, we’ve killed this person,
and we’ve taken revenge.
Don’t worry.
Your reward
will not be deducted due to this.
Well,
you can pick
any three items from me too.
What’s the matter?
Are you letting him go that easily?
Well...
Let me go after him.
How would you know where he is?
His equipment are quite good.
He doesn’t look
like he’s here to scavenge.
If anything happens,
he’ll surely fix the respawn point
at the nearest city.
Isn’t that common sense?
Besides,
he lost two agile equipment to us.
His speed has decreased.
Can you give me some equipment?
For speed.
Sure!
I have one with me.
Thanks for that.
Everyone.
I announce
that our current goals
will be scavenging,
attacking the bosses,
and killing Deception.
Buddy.
It’s rare
that our captain likes you.
Are you interested to join us?
Why aren’t you talking?
Are you still considering the offer?
I’ll count to three. Is this enough?
Three.
I don’t understand what you’re saying.
We’re a new team.
I’d like to know
if you’d be interested to join us.
I’m not interested.
That’s quite sleazy.
A talent.
Buddy.
Join Team Happy.
I’ll lead you to win
the Professional Challenge League.
You’re so annoying.
I told you. I’m not...
[Player: Su Mucheng.
Happy.Cleansing Mist. Job: Launcher.]
He’s so skillful.
It’s a waste of him being a scavenger.
He should apply his abilities
to better use.
I’m establishing a team.
Do you want to join us?
Salary will be provided.
There are free meals
and accommodation too.
You’re quite skillful.
It’s a waste for you to be a scavenger.
I never collect trash.
That is because you’ve never
seen the true Ultimate materials.
For instance, my weapon.
Have you seen it?
You’re so annoying.
Calm down.
I haven’t shown you everything yet.
He’s dead.
I was too engrossed in the conversation
and forgot about his life.
God Ye.
There’s a boss
in the sewer at Hesin City.
There’s only a small guild.
After you join us,
we’ll fire the bullets.
Small guild?
I suddenly have an idea.
[Chatting with Loulan Slash]
What?
Extend our collaboration.
[Hesin City’s sewer. LV55 Training Zone]
Hurry up.
Increase the firepower.
Else when the big guilds come,
we won’t be able to get anything.
Hello there!
Are you busy?
Lord Grim?
Looks like our effort
will go to waste again, Captain.
I can’t take this anymore.
There, there.
We’re here to discuss
about a potential collaboration.
Do you want to join us?
Each of you will get the materials.
The big guilds always get the bosses.
We couldn’t snatch the bosses
from the big guilds.
Only when they are
having internal disputes
can we get to oust the boss.
Hurry up and attack!
Someone stole the boss.
Aren’t you upset?
Why can’t the small guilds
get the chance to oust the bosses?
We can establish
a competent team.
Do you want to join us?
I want to join your team, God Ye.
Count me in.
Me too.
[The Glory Canteen]
These are the rewarded materials.
Please check.
Looking forward to working with you.
God Ye.
Our team has
more members than Blue Brook Guild now.
[LV 60. Over-world boss.
Ocean Nightwalker. Gan Lie]
[Player: Xu Boyuan. Blue Brook Guild.]
There are a lot of guilds that came today.
[Blue Bridge Spring Snow. Job: Blade Master.]
It seems like
it requires more effort now.
Buddy.
[Chatting with Electric Youfeng]
Let’s join forces to oust the Excellent Dynasty.
[Chatting with Araceae]
Tyranny sent us a message earlier.
They want to join forces to attack you.
I don’t really like this act.
Let’s join forces to oust them then.
[Chatting with Moonlight Army]
Help us out.
Let’s oust Tyranny together.
We’ll take the lead.
You can come in as the support.
As if I would buy into it.
No worries.
Okay.
Sure.
That’s why I don’t want
to get involved in such disputes.
Let’s buy some time
while waiting for
the guild leader’s main force.
Let’s wait at leisure
while the enemy labors.
Lord Grim.
[He Wu.Martial Know-it-all]
He Wu.
Heavenly Justice.
[Yue Yun.Yue Ziqin.
Zhao Hua.Flowing Stream]
[Yue Yun.Yue Ziqin.]
Yue Yun.
[Zhao Hua.Flowing Stream]
Zhao Hua.
My fellow guild leaders.
This marks our first collaboration.
Let’s do something big.
[Next episode’s preview]
Congratulations to Samsara
for winning the competition!
They’ve created history.
Oh, Deception is online.
Tang, Bao, come on!
That’s odd.
Weren’t they all negative?
They’re against so many people.
Of course they couldn’t win.