Online Drama Distribution License
(Shanghai) Online Content Review No. 045 (2023)
Issuing Authority: Shanghai Municipal Radio and Television Bureau
Produced by Tencent Video
The King's Avatar
Let great stories live on forever
Adapted from the novel "The King's Avatar" by Butterfly Blue, an author of Yuewen Group's Qidian Reading.
Original reading platform: Qidian Qidian Reading
This work is adapted from the original novel The King's Avatar by Yuewen Group. All characters, visuals, videos, music, and other elements in the series are the intellectual property of Shanghai Yuewen Film & Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
No individual, organization, or institution may reproduce, modify, record, edit, or use any part of this work in any form without prior written authorization from Yuewen. Any infringement will be pursued to the fullest extent of the law, and violators will be held legally accountable and liable for all resulting economic losses.
Samsara!
This shot was so cool!
This is Zhou Zekai.
The Gun King, Cloud Piercer.
Dear viewers,
This is the second round of Grand Finals
of Season 8 of the Glory Professional Alliance League.
I don't think that Blue Rain will win this round.
This is the first match of the individual challenge.
But the game has only just started!
And it might end very quickly too.
Why?
Are they that strong just because of the skill point boost?
Not really.
It's mostly because of their strategy.
Right now, whoever scores 10 points first
will become the champion.
During the first half of the match,
Samsara 7.5 to 2.
[Individual Challenge] [Group Challenge] [Team Challenge] [Total]
Single-Round Score
Blue Rain is very passive.
If they want to win,
aside from winning the group challenge and the team challenge,
they need to score at least one point
[Total score 9.5]
to secure overtime with Samsara.
[Overtime]
So there's still hope to win.
Blue Rain's strength is their strategy.
Playing it safe and stalling for time might do it for them.
So it's crucial for them to score this point in the individual challenge.
And Yu Feng
is the one that is trusted to score that point.
Unfortunately,
his opponent is Samsara's ace,
Zhou Zekai.
[Glory]
Zhou Zekai is the first to compete in the individual challenge.
Samsara's so bold and daring!
They are quite confident of winning the tournament.
Why didn't they let Huang Shaotian on the stage?
According to the rules,
each member can only play twice.
Shaotian probably is their main defender and core player.
Yu Wenzhou's hand speed puts him at disadvantage in the individual challenge.
Yu Feng is their best chance
To keep their strength
it's up
to you now.
So the only ones who can join the individual challenge
are the backup players.
Samsara
has decided to no longer have Zhou Zekai guard their base.
They will be represented
by the best player in their team.
[Finals of Glory Professional Alliance]
Samsara won the round again.
[Individual Challenge]
Samsara won yet another round!
Oh wow!
The upcoming last round is going to be the match point.
If Samsara wins again,
this will be the first time in Glory's history
that the finals end prematurely.
Let's congradulate Samsara
for winning the competition!
They create history.
This is Samsara's first champion title
in the Glory Professional Alliance.
They are also the fifth team to get this title.
So now,
the 8th Glory Professional Alliance Challenge League.
Let's give a round of applause
Shaotian.
Let's join them too.
to our champion!
Team Samsara!
It's a pity that the competition ends earlier.
I didn't expect Samsara to be aggressive during the individual match.
As the ace for Blue Rain,
the finals has ended before you joined the individual match, Huang Shaotian.
Do you
have anything you would like to say?
I have nothing to say.
I don't want to say anything.
That chatterbox Huang Shaotian has nothing to say?
failed to win the competition
It must be pretty disappointing
Then let us ask captain Yu Wenzhou
Shaotian has nothing to say.
What else can I say?
Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Heavenly Domain Level 55 Training Zone]
Blue Rain and Samsara were really fighting fiercely!
The master is scavenging again!
I cannot really understand God Ye.
Oh, he noticed me!
So that's then how the god-level observation skill looks like?
He's should be too far away to hear me speak!
He shouldn't have heard me.
[Chatting with Homeward Bound.
I saw Deception. He's at Oak City.]
[Chatting with Loulan Slash]
The daily quests have been updated.
[A guild member saw Deception, God Ye.]
What's wrong?
[Gosh, he's at Oak City.]
Deception has signed in.
Boss.
Log in and come look for us
I'll give you the items in the bag.
Is it full?
Almost.
First we go and intercept Deception
If the bag is too full, it'll affect my speed.
Okay.
Wow, you scavenged all of that by yourself!
And where is Deception?
I received news
that he's now at Oak City.
Are we rushing there?
No use.
There's a guild war there.
If Deception wants to scrap-pick, he won't miss this place.
Let's find a suitable scrap-picking spot to ambush him.
Clever.
But you haven't finished unloading your bags.
Hold on, I'll make another trip first.
Why do they gather there?
Save the trouble.
Lou.
Are you here to scrap-pick as well?
You haven't filled up your bag yet, right?
I...
I'm not here to scavenge,
God Ye.
What a coincidence.
Why don't you help to unload Bun's and Tang's bags?
As a guild leader,
unloading a scrap-picker's bag?
Might as well be a scrap-picker
[Trade complete!]
This guy is also really good at carrying things.
He's a plate armour class.
His weight limit is high to begin with.
Then can return to Happy Guild with Chasing Haze first, Lou.
Okay.
What?
I need to carry these to your guild?
Let's go.
I'll show you the way.
Deception will be here soon.
The others will come with me.
Let's make an ambush.
That's odd.
He was here earlier.
He was carrying a heavy load.
He couldn't run too far.
I found him.
I'll make you return it to me with interest.
Boss.
Are we really not going to disguise ourselves?
No use.
Why isn't Deception here yet?
That's odd.
Didn't they hit their load limit?
Tang.
Bun.
Go after him.
This isn't right.
How can they follow me?
Don't snatch it.
Don't finish him just yet.
You know, you are really taking ruthlessness to a new level
You actually dared to ambush us.
Why
aren't you affected by the load?
So you thought that you could exploit the fact we carry a heavy load
and so you ambushed us on purpose?
Unfortunately,
if you had more friends and better intel,
your information wouldn't be outdated.
We've unloaded our bags earlier.
You're so daring.
That's why, you see
The thing with online games
is that it's very tiresome tome play them on your own.
Still trying to run?
Don't even think of escaping.
Like I said last time,
would you be interested to join us?
[Exit the game]
Rather than keep sneaking around
Better to follow us and do things together
How is it?
Dot tell me he just closed the game.
Boss.
What should we do?
What else can we do?
We'll keep persuading him.
Let's go scarp-picking first.
We need to fill our warehouse.
The title is then Samsara's.
You have to admit it!
If you're so cool, come beat me in the game
Lord...
Lord Grim.
[Player: Liang Yichun. Blue Brook's guild's guild leader. Account: Changing Spring. ]
What's wrong with Blue Bridge?
[Job: Berserker]
Lord...
Lord Grim is leading his team
to do the scrap-picking
amidst the fight
That's not scrap-picking.
He's literally snatching our items.
He's outright bullying people
What if he's a God-level player?
There are only the three of them.
Charge!
Why are the members
of the Blue Brook Guild charging towards us?
It's probably because we're keeping a high profile while crap-picking.
[Lord Grim]
What's the matter with you?
Why are you chasing us away?
I should be asking you this question.
You're following us and it's very stressful.
Nonsense.
[Blue River ]
We're scrap-picking.
Who do we follow, if not you?
We chase scrap-pickers away.
Do you find it surprising?
You'll regret this.
Is this a threat?
No.
[Blue River]
It's a notice.
Just you wait.
They refuse to let us scavenge.
They're catching up with us.
What do we do now?
Do you want to fight with them?
They are among the top players in the game.
A bit of practice won't hurt.
The worst situation is that we'll die
and lose some XP and equipment.
Retreat first, boss.
We'll cover for you.
So they're rushing towards us.
I suspect they're scheming something.
Attack at full power!
Wait...
Did they just die?
Why on earth did they come here?
[Happy Cybercafe]
How did it feel?
There were too many opponents.
I couldn't win.
You fought with so many people at once.
Of course you couldn't win.
In that situation,
you must take advantage of every condition available.
Maneuver warfare.
Consider this part of the training for the Challenge League.
Guys, come here for a second.
Have a look.
What's this?
What?
What is this?
A summary of the achievements for capturing world bosses.
Well done, well done
It has only been a week.
You sure are efficient.
We've been very productive this week.
That's a lot.
Just the day before yesterday alone,
our guild alliance managed to capture seven bosses.
Although the materials were divided equally between five groups,
as we took down a lot of bosses,
our total gain is probably bigger than a big guild's.
The responsibility is heavy and the road is long.
Keep it up.
Those medium-sized guilds that couldn't snatch the bosses must be hating us to death.
That's cruel.
The loot is way bigger than I expected.
Perhaps we can create miracles in the Challenge League.
I knew it. You're the best.
I hereby announce
[Excellent Era]
that the Captain of Thunderclap,
an All-Star player,
the master of tactics, Xiao Shiqin,
has already transferred to Excellent Era.
I believe that his joining the team
will surely allow every member of Excellent Era
to become seamlessly embedded into a perfect tactical system.
Did he really transfer to Excellent Era?
We're doomed.
They even hired security.
Excellent Era is making quite a show of force this time.
[Excellent Era]
They're so noisy!
Welcome.
How do you feel about the transfer?
Leaving Thunderclap
fills me with regret.
The transfer
poses as a new challenge to me too.
Now that I'm here,
I look forward to working together with my new teammates
and supporters
to walk together with Excellent Era out of its slump
to regain the glory of a triple championship
Reopening this new era\
Reuniting with my heart's desire
Where my passion lies
My dream is still rampant
A fallen star that is still hopeful
Sparks fly, the fingers that wake up
a soul that's unafraid of the darkness
Until we carry all before it
and return to glory
Exclaiming glory,
breaking the cycle of fate
Perhaps the hardships
could make us tougher
Seeing my own reflection in the sweat
No turning back
A match with no retreats
Seize the moment
Against all odds until the end
You took away
My reason to give up
Let the wild dream revive our memories
Youth is beyond nostalgic
It's to transcend the future
Yet still striving for more