Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Excellent Era]
Captain Liu.
I tried to ask Cui Li about it discreetly.
He didn't reply though.
However,
if Xiao Shiqin is coming,
your position as the Vice-Captain might be...
Captain Liu.
Look at my background.
Everyone in Excellent Era
is my men.
Xiao Shiqin
is just a bumpkin from Thunderclap.
How dare he try to take away my position as the Vice-Captain?
By the way,
he's quite capable.
Our team's results are currently very bad.
If Xiao Shiqin didn't join us,
I'd want to leave.
Let's
have a match with Xiao Shiqin later.
Have a seat.
Our club has an announcement to make.
Xiao Shiqin is joining us, isn't he?
The two of you.
Well,
as part of the deal, you'll be switching to Thunderclap.
Pack your stuff
in these three days.
You may leave on Monday, July 1st.
You're kicking me out now that I'm of no use to you?
Are you dumping me now after the club used me?
How did the club use you?
Well...
Without my help,
how could you kick Ye Qiu out?
I'm going to report to the media.
No.
No way.
The club will surely deny this.
Then, I'd be the scapegoat.
What if I don't want to go?
This is an exchange of members.
If we cancel the deal,
[Termination of Contract]
do you want to break your contract?
Or,
do you want to retire as well?
I'll terminate the contract.
[Excellent Era]
Hurry up.
The media is arriving soon.
A little bit upwards.
Are you leaving?
Thank you for your contribution to the club.
[Welcome, Xiao Shiqin]
Well...
What are you doing?
Why are you so careless?
Do they think I can't do anything about it if I'm made to take the side door?
Never mind.
You don't mind,
but I do.
Look over here.
Your Excellent Era's Vice-Captain is here.
[Excellent Era]
It's red light now.
Please follow the traffic rules.
Stop when the traffic light is red.
[Excellent Era]
The light is green now,
you may go.
Liu Hao.
So the fans still saw me...
Good morning.
Why is it him?
If I had known we'd run into him, I'd have avoided passing Happy.
You're early too.
Well, the club has something important happening.
I can't possibly sleep in.
It's so annoying.
I'm not as chill as you are.
Xiao Shiqin!
Xiao Shiqin! Xiao Shiqin!
Is Xiao Shiqin's transfer related to you too?
Of course it is.
As the Vice-Captain of Excellent Era,
I welcome high-level players to join Excellent Era.
To this end,
you even exchanged yourself for him?
Of course.
I...
How did you know?
Why wouldn't I know?
Wait...
Did Su Mucheng tell you?
Didn't you plan to leave Excellent Era since the start?
I'm a little unlucky now,
but I'm still better than you.
At least I still get to participate in the professional matches next season.
What about you?
Unlucky?
I don't think so.
I think your luck is getting better.
What did you say?
If you stay in Excellent Era,
you won't get to join any matches in the next season.
Excellent Era wants to make a comeback through the Challenge Round,
but regrettably,
the slot belongs to us.
You're really full of yourself.
I'd like to see who will lose the round, then.
It will be even more interesting if both teams are ousted together.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed, then.
Farewell.
Aren't you
that someone?
Who is he?
He's Excellent Era's...
That...
That guy.
That guy?
I know!
Liu Gao!
Stop bothering him, Wei Chen.
He's rushing to take Bus Route 9.
The bus is here.
Hurry up and board the bus.
By the way, Wei Chen,
his name is pronounced as Hao.
Don't say that you're my friend.
Bao.
Stay away from him.
Yes,
boss.
Is it pronounced as Hao?
Well,
I can't believe that it's not Gao.
Are we
leaving?
Why are we taking the Bus Route 9?
We'll take the taxi!
Xiao Shiqin! Xiao Shiqin!
Look at this scale.
He's indeed big.
That's enough.
Let's not bother about them.
We still have things to do.
The battle to snatch the boss for the new week is approaching.
Xiao Shiqin! Xiao Shiqin!
Hello, everyone.
[League Weekly]
We'll report
the latest updates on the teams.
Please stay tuned.
Yifan.
I'm sorry.
I...
I can't do anything.
Yingjie.
Although I'm not in Tiny Herb's plan,
I have my own plans.
I plan to go to a cybercafe.
Cybercafe?
You're going to give up, aren't you, Yifan?
No.
I'm going to a place
to continue training
and improve my skills.
But...
Don't worry.
I'll be back.
However,
by then,
we might no longer be teammates.
It's okay.
We'll still be friends.
You're right.
[Excellent Era]
From today onwards,
Xiao Shiqin
will be joining Excellent Era as the Vice-Captain,
and he will strive together with us.
Let's strive for the Repechage Round!
Sure!
Mucheng.
Why are you acting like Zhou Zekai today?
You're the OGs from the first generation of the team.
Please look after him.
Okay.
Is this the vibe of a wealthy team?
Xiao Shiqin, Sun Xiang.
I'll bring you to somewhere later.
The rest of you may leave.
Where are we going?
[Happy Cybercafe]
It's just nearby.
Boss.
Someone is looking for you.
Who is it?
Bring them up.
Is this your training room?
It's quite decent.
Who is this?
Ye Qiu.
Shiqin is here.
Xiao Shiqin?
Well.
No wonder he looks familiar.
Who are you?
I'm Wei Chen.
The former captain of Blue Rain.
That's right.
It's me.
Wei Chen.
I never heard of you.
Who are you?
Duh.
Of course you didn't know me.
You were still playing with mud then.
What did you say?
So you're Captain Wei Chen.
Apologies, nice to meet you.
We've met somewhere else, haven't we?
Who are you?
Tao Xuan.
CEO of Excellent Era, right?
That's right.
When is Excellent Era disbanding?
Why should it be disbanded?
It's ousted, of course it should be disbanded.
You're Shiqin, right?
You seem all right.
But why are you so foolish?
Excellent Era is going down.
Yet, you hopped on the boat.
Are you trying to drown along with them?
Ye.
If I'm up against Excellent Era during the Challenge Round,
I won't go easy on them.
Only if Excellent Era gets to be our opponent.
I should be the one
telling you this.
What brings you here?
It's nothing.
I was just bringing our Captain and Vice-Captain to visit their seniors.
I wonder if you have any advice for them.
Advice?
Let's have a friendly match.
Who's going first?
I thought we're playing together?
I...
I don't think we need to have a match now.
We'll eventually meet during the league.
We're just here
to greet the seniors.
Boss.
Someone is looking for you.
Who is it?
He said he's Qiao Yifan.
Yifan is here?
Well,
do you want to have a drink?
Come on.
Let's go and have a look.
Senior.
Boy.
Not bad.
You're quite polite.
He's considered your senior.
Wei Chen.
Have you heard of him?
Hello, senior.
Great!
Bao.
Soft Mist.
You met each other online.
This is
our boss,
Chen Guo.
You're here.
Your accommodation is arranged.
Later, Wei Chen and Bao will bring you there.
Leave this to me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Xiao Shiqin.
Sun Xiang.
He's really Sun Xiang.
He's Xiao Shiqin.
Hurry up and come over.
Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin are at Happy Cybercafe.
Oh, no!
It's too chaotic.
I don't think they would take advantage and leave without paying, right?
Did I cause trouble?
What a pity.
It's quite expensive.
It's damaged.
It's okay if the glasses are broken.
Will they be all right?
I know you'll be successful.
Should we go across the road to get security from Excellent Era?
Cui Li.
Ask for help now.
Stop squeezing!
We're at Happy.
[Happy Cybercafe]
We're at Happy!
I have been waiting
outside the door of my dream
For you to come back one day
Full of honor and love
The cold winter announces
the end of glory
Snow covers the night
Embracing pure sincerity
Turn around and leave
The dawn probably
doesn't want to come just yet
I have my own plans
I won't leave my life in others' hands
Explore the most powerful secrets
in a new world
The weak ripples will gradually
turn into huge waves, shocking the world
Onto the stage, overcome obstacles,
and fight without defeat
My heart is racing,
beyond success or failure
I will gain more than that
Get brighter and more exciting
The past and the future
carry each other
The glorious era
No one can replace
what is precious now
Everyone who leaves unwillingly
Will come back