Online Drama Distribution License
(Shanghai) Online Content Review No. 045 (2023)
Issuing Authority: Shanghai Municipal Radio and Television Bureau
Produced by Tencent Video
The King's Avatar
Let great stories live on forever
Adapted from the novel "The King's Avatar" by Butterfly Blue, an author of Yuewen Group's Qidian Reading.
Original reading platform: Qidian Qidian Reading
This work is adapted from the original novel The King's Avatar by Yuewen Group. All characters, visuals, videos, music, and other elements in the series are the intellectual property of Shanghai Yuewen Film & Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
No individual, organization, or institution may reproduce, modify, record, edit, or use any part of this work in any form without prior written authorization from Yuewen. Any infringement will be pursued to the fullest extent of the law, and violators will be held legally accountable and liable for all resulting economic losses.
It's just starting over again, from the beginning
The fire of our dreams
it illuminating the present
Our passion and resolve
remain unchanged
Eagerly looking forward
The journey to the summit begins
with anticipation
Believe, and you will surely overcome every difficulty
Teamwork has slowly become our habit
Myriad of opportunities
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills leave people amazed
See you there this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Enjoying the competition
Chasing after the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The flow of the match ever-changing
Seizing the control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
My favourite part is when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can make me stop
The King’s Avatar S3
Captain Xiao.
Good morning!
[Excellent Era]
Are you going home for the holiday?
Yeah.
To unwind a bit.
Xiao Shiqin.
Are you going to stay in the club the whole summer?
Well, I just came.
I want look around and get used to the place.
Su Mucheng.
Happy holidays!
I'm leaving.
Have fun!
Goodbye.
Mucheng.
Going to Happy?
You too?
I'm just taking a stroll.
Ye.
There's someone looking for you.
Oh, you're here.
Welcome.
At last, I am fully on holiday!
Ummm...
Hello.
You're here too, Shiqin.
I have nothing to do.
So I came to visit.
You just joined a new team.
Shouldn't you be bonding with your teammates
instead of rushing to gather intel on your enemies?
So dedicated!
The whole team is gone on a holiday.
I have no one to bond with.
Do not speak to this guy!
Be careful, he can steal our information!
You're too direct, senior Ye.
Stealing information?
You're indeed checking us out.
No...
I don't!
I'm only having a look.
Senior,
have a drink.
Thanks.
Bun.
There's nothing to hide.
Sit down.
Oh.
Getting used to Excellent Era?
I just came,
Still getting used.
In the challenge match you'll be facing us.
Are you confident?
I guess so.
If you lose to us,
that would really be terrible.
What will you do then?
You're not joining Excellent Era
only because you want to play in the challenge league only, right?
I will do my best.
That's the right attitude.
What are you doing?
Killing the boss.
You are not busy at the moment, right, Xiao?
Then
lend us a hand.
This isn't appropriate.
Never mind, then.
No.
This might be
a chance to observe Happy's abilities.
However, I'm quite bored.
Let me play a bit.
Boss,
bring him a Mechanic account card.
You know, I'll play for a bit too.
Sure!
Mucheng, come sit here then.
You can use my account.
I knew it.
She was waiting for this!
Did I just end up setting the example?
She's so cunning.
[Glory]
[Level 70 World Boss.
Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr]
Captain Zhang.
Vice-Captain here.
We have the boss under control.
Should the mobile unit attack as well?
Hold on.
Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade
Four Guild Alliance is approaching.
Has anyone seen Ye Qiu?
We haven't seen Enlightened Lord yet.
Okay.
Watch their movements.
Be careful during the operation.
If you spot Ye Qiu,
show no mercy.
Attack!
Charge!
Mobile unit,
support the right side.
Come on!
The defense is broken.
Their commander is great.
Take advantage when their defense is down
and attack them now.
Over there.
The retreat is a bit too much.
No.
Why on Earth I am so involved?
I should only be observing Ye Qiu's teammates.
Don't panic.
Restore the defense formation.
There's space to advance and retreat.
It's so strategic.
Could it be...
Who's leading Tyranny?
Zhang Xinjie.
Who else?
The strategies are well-thought-out
and can create trouble for any team.
Mechanic.
Could it be
Xiao Shiqin?
How come this guy is with Ye Qiu?
There's an ace.
Ace?
The left side is in danger.
Is it Ye Qiu?
[Player: Ye Xiu. Happy.
Let There Be Light. Job: Battle Mage]
Player: Ye Xiu
Let There Be Light
Job: Battle Mage
This...
This is...
2. Short-Lived Weft
3. Singularly Arrogant Smoke
4. Kurara
5. Rampant Windrider
Look at the way these two fight together.
It must be Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng.
It can't be anyone else.
What date is it today?
[Monday, July 3. Good for meeting friends]
[and spending time outdoors.
Avoid other activities.]
[Do not stay at home
or make transactions.]
[Not suitable for openings, launches,
or moving into a new house.]
Am I playing the online game
or a Professional Alliance match?
[System Announcement. Heavenly Justice]
Congratulations to Heavenly Justice,
[defeated LV70 World Boss,]
Congratulations to Heavenly Justice
[Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr]
for defeating
Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr.
Awesome!
I heard you cheering.
Of course!
It drops the material I need to upgrade my Death's Hand.
Why are you leaving so soon?
Let's play together a bit more.
No, thanks.
I have to go back now.
I need to prepare a lot of things for the team.
What you can possibly do with everyone being on holiday?
Let's do one more.
Didn't I just join?
I need to familiarize myself with a lot of things.
[Zhang Xinjie]
Hello?
I've made up my mind.
I'll spend my holiday at Happy this time.
Okay, sure!
Welcome.
Hello.
Are you busy?
Radiant and Parade were led by you,
weren't they?
Yes, it was me.
How come you've joined the battle on their side?
Well, it's just that we will be facing them
in the challenge league.
I just wanted to check what they really are like.
How does he handle them, then?
They're mostly newbies.
Newbies?
[Happy Internet Cafe]
Then it's really not easy to get a good read of them.
However,
Ye Qiu wouldn't let me see too much of their confidential stuff.
I didn't see anything related to their systematic training either.
Seems like Ye Qiu is doing a good job.
To the point that you got wary
and had to go check them out in person.
[Excellent Era]
Excellent Era's vast collection of assets and accounts
by right, are not something easy for a makeshift troupe to catch up to.
However, the problem
is that within this makeshift troupe,
there's Ye Qiu, the ace player.
He is familiar with every aspect of Glory.
Speaking of this,
if Su Mucheng doesn't stay at Excellent Era,
the All-Star account, Dancing Rain,
might be brought away too.
If she joins Happy...
If Dancing Rain joins Happy,
it'll happen a year later.
Then, we'll have the results of the Challenge League tournament.
There's only one winner
in the fight between Excellent Era and Happy.
[Xiao Shiqin
The call had ended]
Ye Qiu has been out of the professional alliance
for seven months now.
Captain Han.
Look who I brought here.
You're finally here.
[Happy Internet Cafe]
[47 days until application day
for the challenge round. All the best!]
Do the boss first, then go after Zhang Xinjie.
Sure.
Tyranny is holding a press conference right now.
Lin Jingyan has transferred to Tyranny.
Lin Jingyan?
[Tyranny]
I debuted as a professional player
in Season 2.
I didn't shine like other ace players did
during their rookie years.
Step by step, I've made it here.
Perhaps retirement
is my best option.
I almost made that decision.
However, an out-of-the-blue call
made me change my mind.
Come join us.
We have a place for you.
I, a professional player who almost retired,
am returning to pursue the championship.
If there's a team that needs me,
I am ready to accept the challenge.
I hereby announce
that Lin Jingyan
will be an important part of Tyranny's roster in next season.
The club right now is preparing a new Brawler account for him.
Our only reason for inviting Lin Jingyan into our team
is winning the championship.
How annoying.
Annoying?
It has nothing to do with us now.
Zhang Xinjie personally led the team to kill the boss,
most likely it's for this Brawler account Lin Jingyan is going to use.
Wind Howl's Ex-Captain Lin Jingyan
Transfers to Tyranny
Who's the Successor of God-Level
Account, Demon Subduer?
Lin Jingyan is joining their team.
Given his personality,
he wouldn't bear to see Zhang Xinjie working hard for him
while he sits back and enjoys the results.
Do you mean that he'll start coming as well?
Lin Jingyan.
Did he had a habit of going to sleep on schedule?
Unbearable!
[Hundred Blossoms'
All-Star player, Tang Hao,]
[transfers to Wind Howl for 10 million]
[Blue Rain's All-Star player, Yu Feng,]
[transfers to Hundred Blossoms
for six million]
[For whom will Hundred Blossoms
sign the ten million cheque]
[to become the player
of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms?]
The transfer window
is closing soon.
The news these days is quite boring.
What's the matter?
I'll have a look.
The ace account of Hundred Blossoms,
Spitfire, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms,
is bought by Tyranny for 16 million?
Breaking the Glory's historical record.
Are you serious?
16 million for an account?
Not for a player,
but an account?
Must be me seeing things.
What is Tyranny trying to do?
They sold their core player
and ace account.
Next,
why won't Hundred Blossoms change their name
and start afresh like a new team to boot?
This is insane.
They are literally starting afresh.
Both teams have gone crazy.
Tyranny really is spending big.
They bought all Hundred Blossoms' poster figures.
Hundred Blossoms' fans
must be heartbroken.
That's for Zhang Jiale.
He's joining Tyranny as well?
Zhang Jiale is joining to chase the champion's title.
He wants to join the team with real prospects
of winning the tournament.
And in the alliance, the teams who has such a potential
by any count
are not that many.
Han Wenqing.
Lin Jingyan.
Zhang Jiale.
Are all running out of time.
But they desire to become the champion more than anything else.
There is no way out for them anymore.
This team.
Seriously.
Did this bunch
had this already planned from the beginning?
Zhang Jiale has been with Hundred Blossoms for six years.
How could he...
It's so unexpected.
How could Zhang Jiale do this?
We have one more piece of great news to announce today.
Look, look!
An ace player has joined us in the venue today.
What?
He's about to join Tyranny.
It's Zhang Jiale.
They must be joking.
He's joining Tyranny?!
I've never heard anything about it.
Are they for real?
I'll be making a comeback in the new season.
I've already signed the contract with Tyranny.
In the new season,
I'll be playing for Tyranny
Are Hundred Blossoms brain-dead or what?
How could they give up on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms?
They're disrespecting the fans.
If I were you, I couldn't accept it either.
The club owes the fans a proper explanation.
I have a question.
Speaking for loyal Hundred Blossoms fans,
the club has sold off their most beloved character,
and their favourite player
has transferred to another team.
Do you have anything you want to say to the fans who have been supporting you?
[Hundred Blossoms]
I apologise for retiring irresponsibly in the previous season.
I also apologize for making a comeback this season
with a team
other than Hundred Blossoms.
An apology and nothing else?
Your retirement and comeback both were rushed and sudden.
It took a lot of people by surprise.
You broke the hearts of Hundred Blossoms' fans.
Why did you make such a decision?
Because
I want to become a champion.
Lin Jingyan, who has never made it to the finals.
Zhang Jiale, who has lost three finals out of three.
And Han Wenqing, who never gives up.
They have no time.
They have no opportunity.
They have no way out.
Their only desire is to become the champions.
Only then they chose to burn everything in this last attempt.
Their desire to win surpasses everything else.
Just like all Glory Professional Alliance players
To a man.
The battle is spiraling out of control
The Blue is stunned, surrounded on all sides, struggle is useless
Caught in a trap
The cold rain approaches in full fury
The lonely knight waves his sword
fighting for his dream
There's surely a loophole
in the encirclement
Invisible shadow, shaking earth
The continuous cheer is deafening
The prey disappears in a flash!
This deed
Failure is not an option
Who will become a champion?
In a blink of an eye
Leaving behind all the rivals?
Let the fingertips fly
Slashing through the sky
Riding on the wind
Breaking all limits and rules
No regret
If we're drawn to meet
at the battlefield
We'll still take it easy
Come on
Come where the light reflects on a sword's surface
Charge towards the target
And attack
Strive for success
Let's forget
All the pain
For the winner is the king
Who will claim victory?