Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
Captain Xiao.
Good morning!
[Excellent Era]
Are you going home for the holiday?
Yes.
Just to wind down.
Xiao Shiqin.
Are you going to stay in the club the entire summer?
I just came.
I want to get familiar with the environment.
Su Mucheng.
Happy holidays!
I'm leaving.
Have fun!
Goodbye.
Mucheng.
Are you going to Happy?
You too?
I'm just taking a stroll.
Ye.
You have a guest.
You're here.
Welcome.
I'm finally getting a holiday.
Well...
Hello.
You're here too, Shiqin.
I'm bored.
So I came to visit.
You just joined the team.
Not only do you not bond with your teammates,
but you also rush to check out your enemies.
You're really dedicated.
The team is on a holiday now.
I have no one to bond with.
Let's not talk to him.
He might pry for our information.
You're too direct, Ye.
Prying for information?
You're indeed checking us out.
No...
It's nothing.
I'm just having a look.
Xiao.
Have a drink.
Thanks.
Bao.
There's nothing to hide.
Have a seat.
Oh.
How are you adapting to Excellent Era?
I just joined the team,
hence I'm still adapting.
We're your opponent for the challenge round.
Are you confident?
I guess so.
If you lose to us,
it'd look bad.
What should you do then?
You're not joining Excellent Era
to play for the challenge round only, right?
I will do my best.
That's the right attitude.
What are you doing?
Defeating the boss.
You have nothing to do, right, Xiao?
Come on.
Help me out.
This isn't appropriate.
Never mind, then.
No.
This can be
a chance to observe Happy's ability.
However, I'm quite bored.
Let me play a round.
Boss.
Give him a Mechanic character card.
I'll play one round, then.
Sure!
You can have a seat here, Mucheng.
Use my account.
I knew it.
She's waiting for this.
Did I just become the one who started this?
She's so cunning.
[Glory]
[Level 70. Over-world Boss.
Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr]
Captain Zhang.
I'm the Vice-Captain.
We've controlled the boss.
Should the mobile unit attack as well?
Hold on.
Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade
are approaching.
Has anyone seen Ye Qiu?
We haven't seen Enlightened Lord yet.
Okay.
Watch their whereabouts.
Be careful during the operation.
If you spot Ye Qiu,
show no mercy.
Attack!
Mobile unit.
Support the right lane.
Come on!
The defense is disrupted.
Their commander is great.
Take advantage when their defense is disrupted
and attack them now.
Over there.
The retreat is a bit too much.
No.
Why am I so engrossed?
I should be observing Ye Qiu's teammates.
Don't panic.
Reshuffle the defense formation.
There's space to advance and retreat.
It's so strategic.
Could it be...
Who's leading Tyranny?
Zhang Xinjie.
Who else?
The strategies are well-thought-out
and can create trouble for any teams.
Mechanic.
Could it be
Xiao Shiqin?
Why is he with Ye Qiu?
There's an ace.
Ace?
The left lane is in danger.
Is it Ye Qiu?
[Player: Ye Xiu. Happy.
Let There Be Light. Job: Battle Mage]
This...
Look at the way they fight together.
It must be Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng.
It can't be anyone else.
What day is today?
[Monday, July 3. Good for meeting friends]
[and spending time outdoors.
Avoid other activities.]
[Do not stay at home
or make transactions.]
[Not suitable for openings, launches,
or moving into a new house.]
Am I playing video game
or professional challenge?
[System Announcement. Heavenly Justice]
Congratulations, Heavenly Justice,
[defeated LV70 Over-world Boss,]
[Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr]
for defeating the boss,
Red Cloak Warlock Mirworr.
Awesome!
I heard you cheering.
Of course!
It concerns the material I need to upgrade my Death's Hand.
Why are you leaving so soon?
Let's have another round together.
No, thanks.
I have to go back now.
I need to settle a lot of things for the team.
You're on holiday, there's nothing to do.
Come on, let's have another round.
Didn't I just join?
I need to familiarize myself with a lot of things.
[Zhang Xinjie]
Hello?
I've made up my mind.
I'll spend my holiday at Happy this time.
Okay, sure!
Welcome.
Hello.
Are you busy?
You're the one who was commanding Radiant and Parade,
aren't you?
Yes, it was me.
Why did you join their team?
Well, they're our opponents
for the challenge round.
I was just checking them out.
How is his team, then?
They're mostly newbies.
Newbies?
[Happy Cybercafe]
It's hard to gauge their abilities, then.
However,
Ye Qiu won't show me their confidential stuff.
I didn't see anything about their systematic training plans.
Seems like Ye Qiu is doing a good job.
You even got wary
and went to check them out in person.
[Excellent Era]
Excellent Era's vast asset and accounts
are not easy for a makeshift troupe to surpass.
However, the problem
is that within this makeshift troupe,
there's Ye Qiu, the ace player.
He witnessed every bit of Glory.
Speaking of this,
if Su Mucheng didn't stay at Excellent Era,
the All-Star account, Dancing Rain,
might be brought away too.
If she joins Happy...
If Dancing Rain joins Happy,
it'll happen a year later.
Then, we'll have the challenge round results.
There's only one winner
between Excellent Era and Happy.
[Xiao Shiqin]
Ye Qiu has been out of the professional alliance
for seven months now.
Captain Han.
Look who I brought here.
You're finally here.
[Happy Cybercafe]
[47 days until application day
for the challenge round. All the best!]
Defeat the boss first, then go after Zhang Xinjie.
Sure.
Tyranny is having a press conference.
Lin Jingyan has transferred to Tyranny.
Lin Jingyan?
[Tyranny]
I debuted as a professional player
in Season 2.
I didn't shine like other ace players did
during their rookie years.
Step by step, I've made it here.
Perhaps retirement
is my best option.
I almost made that decision.
However, an out-of-the-blue call
made me change my mind.
Come join us.
We have a place for you.
I, a professional player who almost retired,
am returning to pursue the championship.
If the team needs me,
I'll be ready to join the challenge.
I hereby announce
that Lin Jingyan
will play an important role in Tyranny's upcoming season.
The club is now customizing a brand new Brawler account for him.
Our sole purpose in inviting Lin Jingyan into our team
is for the championship.
That's bothersome.
Bothersome?
It has nothing to do with us now.
Zhang Xinjie personally led the team to defeat the boss,
possibly because Lin Jingyan is going to use the Brawler account.
[Former captain of Wind Howl,
Lin Jingyan transfers to Tyranny]
[Who's the successor of]
Lin Jingyan is joining their team.
[God-level account, Demon Subduer?]
Given his character,
he wouldn't bear to see Zhang Xinjie working hard for him
while he sits back and enjoys the results.
Do you mean that he's joining as well?
Lin Jingyan.
Does he has the habit of resting regularly?
Gosh!
[Hundred Blossoms'
All-Star player, Tang Hao,]
[transfers to Wind Howl for 10 million]
[Blue Rain's All-Star player, Yu Feng,]
[transfers to Hundred Blossoms
for six million]
[For whom will Hundred Blossoms
sign the ten million cheque]
[to become the player
of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms?]
The transfer window
is closing soon.
The news these days is quite boring.
What's the matter?
I'll have a look.
The ace account of Hundred Blossoms,
Spitfire, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms,
is bought by Tyranny for 16 million?
It has broken the record in Glory's history.
Are you serious?
16 million for a character?
It's not a player,
but a character?
Am I dreaming?
What is Tyranny trying to do?
They sold their core player
and ace account.
Next,
is Hundred Blossoms going to change their name
and start afresh like a new team?
This is insane.
They are literally starting afresh.
The two teams are crazy.
Tyranny is rich indeed.
They bought Hundred Blossoms' ace player.
Hundred Blossoms' fans
must be heartbroken.
That's for Zhang Jiale.
He's joining Tyranny as well?
Zhang Jiale is joining to become the champion.
He's joining the team with the potential
to become the champion.
There are only a few teams in the alliance
that are likely
to become the champion.
Han Wenqing.
Lin Jingyan.
Zhang Jiale.
They are running out of time.
But they desire to become the champion more than anything else.
There is no way out for them anymore.
This team.
Seriously.
Gosh, did these old players
have this planned from the beginning?
Zhang Jiale has been with Hundred Blossoms for six years.
How would he...
It's so unexpected.
How could Zhang Jiale do this?
We have
Hurry up and look.
another good news
to announce today.
An ace player is with us today.
What?
He's going to join Tyranny.
It's Zhang Jiale.
This must be a joke.
Is he going to joining Tyranny?
I've never heard any news about it.
Is this real?
I'll be making a comeback in the upcoming season.
I've signed the agreement with Tyranny.
I'll be playing for Tyranny
in the upcoming season.
Is Hundred Blossoms dull?
How could they give up on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms?
They're disrespecting the fans.
If I were you, I couldn't accept it either.
The club owes the fans an explanation.
I have a question.
To the loyal Hundred Blossoms fans,
the club has sold off their most beloved character,
and their favourite player
has transferred to another team.
What do you want to say to the fans who have been supporting you?
[Hundred Blossoms]
I apologise for retiring irresponsibly in the previous season.
I also apologize for making a comeback this season
with a different team
than Hundred Blossoms.
Is that all?
Your retirement and comeback are rushed and sudden.
It took a lot of people by surprise.
You've also hurt the Hundred Blossoms' fans.
Why did you make such a decision?
Because
I want to be the champion.
Lin Jingyan, who has never made it to the finals.
Zhang Jiale, who has participated in three finals without winning one.
And Han Wenqing, who never gives up.
They have no time.
They had no chance.
They have no other way out.
Their only desire is to become the champion.
They decided to ignite the last flame of their passion until the end.
Their desire to win surpasses everything else.
Just like every other
Glory Professional Alliance player.
The battle seems to get out of control
Confusing blues, struggling
in a hopeless situation in vain
Trapped in deep water
The cold rain approaches in full fury
The lonely knight waves his sword
for his dreams
There's surely a loophole
within the perimeter
Invisible mirage, shaking earth
The continuous cheer is deafening
Disappearing in a flash
There's only one result
Which is success
Who rules the world
In a blink of an eye
Advancing like there's no resistance?
Let the fingertips fly
Slashing through the sky
Riding on the wind
Breaking through
all rules and constraints
With no heavy hearts
If we're drawn to meet
at the battlefield
We'll still take it easy
Come on
Charge towards the glints of swords
Charge towards the target
And attack
Strive for success
Let's forget
About all the pain
The winner is the king
Who will emerge victorious?