Recently, a piece of news has sparked widespread discussion among Glory fans.
After the end of the seventh season,
Zhang Jiale, the former captain of Hundred Blossoms,
who announced his retirement in despair,
has just made a comeback by joining Tyranny
to fight for the championship once again.
Zhang Jiale debuted in the league's second season.
His God-level Spitfire expert account,
Dazzling Hundred Blossoms,
can be said to be the cornerstone of the Hundred Blossoms team.
His self-created Hundred Blossoms style of play is known
as the most dazzling and romantic style in the league
Hundred Blossoms is a powerhouse that has reached the finals three times.
Such a team is not supported
by just one ace character like Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.
Chaos of Fallen Flowers was
once Glory's number-one Berserker.
He and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms started the era of dual cores.
Hundred Blossoms' captain, Sun Zheping,
and then-vice captain Zhang Jiale created the Bloody Blossom Scenery,
which swept the league in the third season.
However,
the unstoppable Hundred Blossoms duo met a formidable opponent in the finals.
Ye Qiu, controlling One Autumn Leaf,
led Excellent Era to defeat Hundred Blossoms.
Just when the fans were looking forward
to their next season,
Bloody Blossom Scenery's final performance
took everyone by surprise.
[Iv65 Dazzling Hundred Blossoms]
[Iv65 Chaos of Fallen Flowers]
[Iv65 Void Wanderer]
Right now.
Sun,
are you okay?
Can you continue?
Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Happy Cybercafe]
[Challenge League Training Plan]
What's the matter?
What news has come out this time?
Boss,
it is time to register.
Register?
Registration for the challenge league.
It's going to start soon.
[24th One week before the match.]
[29th Pre-match Rest. 31st D-Day.]
All right, then. Let's register.
Is this everyone?
Don't forget Little Cold Hands.
No, I mean
Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light.
Where's Deception?
That fella needs
to be taught a lesson.
You keep killing him.
What exactly are you trying to tell him?
That scavenging has no future
and he should join the professional league.
What kind of logic is that?
When he can't continue doing what he's passionate about,
he might consider my suggestion.
According to recent statistics from An,
that guy's appearances are becoming less frequent.
Did I go overboard with the killing?
Is he so discouraged
he wants to delete his account?
That's possible.
He might have figured out your timing and is avoiding you,
just like how you avoid Zhang Xinjie.
He's adjusted his schedule
to stay out of your way.
Got it.
Lord Grim isn't online at this time.
Tyranny is here to defeat the boss.
Is this the guy he's talking about?
Deception.
That's right.
That's the name.
Look at him sneaking about.
It looks like he's here to scavenge.
Get rid of him now.
Let's not delay killing the boss.
Did they just kill me on purpose?
Really?
The ninja we killed earlier is back again.
Kill him.
[System Prompt]
Congratulations to Tyranny Guild
for defeating the Darknight Glimmer Saul.
Not even a single thing is left.
[Character Friends.
God Said, Let There be Light.]
[Battle Mage. Online]
Why are you online
right after they left?
Is this the guy he's talking about?
Did you plan this together?
Where can we defeat a boss today?
What do you want?
Calm down.
How did today's scavenging go?
See?
If everyone puts their mind to it,
scavenging becomes impossible.
[God Said, Let There Be Light]
Is it fun doing
[Please use polite language]
this meaningless stuff?
Come and join our team.
If you still feel bored,
you can go back to your scavenging.
Okay.
[God Said, Let There be Light]
Is it convenient for you to come to us?
Where are you?
[Lord Grim shared a location]
[Happy Cybercafe]
Boss,
someone is looking for Ye.
What?
At this late hour?
Who's looking for me?
Me,
Deception.
It's really you.
Why are you here at this hour?
I took the midnight flight.
You're really straightforward.
You bought a ticket
and came right away.
What's your name?
Mo Fan.
Do you need an introduction to the team?
Not really.
I'm not very interested.
Temper, huh?
The competition doesn't start until September.
Stay for a month first.
Let's pull an all-nighter
to check out our professional team.
Did you bring anything?
Character card.
Sit here.
[Lv.70 Cleansing Mist]
So you're the Launcher who killed me countless times.
How deceptive.
What's your game ID?
I'm Steamed Bun Invasion.
I'm Soft Mist.
I'm One Inch Ash.
[Lv.70 Cleansing Mist]
Do you want to have some?
Don't be shy.
So, what do you think?
Boring.
Of course.
The match hasn't started yet.
Now it's preparation time.
What do we need to prepare?
For now,
the most important things are
snatching bosses,
gathering materials,
and making silver equipment.
Snatching materials?
[Glory]
The over-world boss for this week is already gone.
Yeah.
So everyone can relax and take a break this week.
The rest will be here soon.
But you can't relax.
You need some training.
Otherwise,
how can you play well in professional matches?
[Happy Cybercafe]
This is Luo Ji,
also known as Concealed Light.
So it's you.
I didn't think you'd actually make it here.
It looks like I didn't misjudge you.
It's all thanks to me.
This is Bao.
You two are pretty close, right?
Of course.
I watched Concealed Light progress.
This is Mo Fan.
He just joined.
Not yet.
Oh, right.
He has not joined yet.
He's here to check out our team.
Do you still need to check out
before joining a top team?
An Wenyi said he'll arrive at 7:35 PM.
[An Wenyi: I'm here]
He sure is punctual.
An Wenyi,
Little Cold Hands.
Boss,
let's register.
[Happy Cybercafe]
And so, the team came together.
There are plenty of pros in the field worth challenging.
I'll do my best to cooperate with every teammate.
I need to practice more
to make sure
every summoning beast is at its best.
This time it's a real pro team.
No more slacking off like before.
Boss,
do I have a chance to be the best Brawler?
Of course.
We depend on you when it comes to surprise attacks
Mo Fan, have you registered?
If you haven't, just register it anyway.
There's no harm in registering anyway.
For the team's name,
let's call it Happy.
It’s a bit plain.
You're the boss.
You decide.
Anyone who objects,
you can kick them out.
[Ye Xiu, Qiao Yifan, Tang Rou, Mo Fan,
Wei Chen, An Wenyi, Bao Rongxin, Luo Ji]
[Challenge League registration submitted]
Happy Guild,
let's go!
[Happy Cybercafe]
The Challenge League
is finally starting.
First up, we have to face Excellent Era.
Say,
we’ve registered.
But seeing the Excellent Era fans coming and going every day,
do we look like we're the major rival?
Well, about this...
Personally, I couldn't care less.
But you kids,
you might end up in tears from all the criticism.
Criticisms?
We can give it right back to them too.
I find it quite amusing.
How domineering.
What about you?
I think
I can handle it.
What about you two?
Me?
I'm already busy enough with my summoning beasts.
I really don't have the energy to care about those things.
I don't think it's all bad.
Being an underdog team,
we can ride on Excellent Era's fame.
It'll bring more attention.
Unbelievable.
If everyone's mentally prepared,
then
I have a plan.
[Happy Cybercafe]
It's free!
Free internet at Happy Cybercafe
to celebrate our guild's establishment.
Until September 1st,
the internet will be free of charge.
Happy Guild's got some strength.
We're confident we'll make it in the professional scene.
We welcome everyone to spar with our team's players.
A cybercafe team
is being this bold.
That shows they don't care about competitors.
Where did these nobodies come from?
They're daydreaming in broad daylight.
Just you wait and see.
That's fast, isn't it?
[Glory]
I lost.
Let me try.
Watch my skills.
Happy's got some skills.
These guys are at a professional level indeed.
They sure have skills.
Nice!
Awesome!
I'm supporting this Happy Guild.
Say,
Excellent Era fans sure are lousy.
You guys at Excellent Era staged the whole Happy Guild thing, didn't you?
I mean, this season you're in the Challenge League.
You need some drama to get attention, right?
Exactly.
That's right.
Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion who played just now,
weren't they following Lord Grim around in District 10?
Lord Grim?
Isn't Lord Grim suspected to be Ye Qiu, the legendary player?
Of course, Lord Grim isn't Ye Qiu anymore.
If he were Ye Qiu,
why would he be competing against Excellent Era?
Regarding Excellent Era fans's recent focus on Happy Guild,
[League Weekly]
[Happy Guild's captain is Ye Qiu,]
[former captain of Excellent Era!]
we've just learned
that their captain, Lord Grim,
is actually the former captain of Excellent Era, Ye Qiu,
who played a crucial role in Excellent Era's success.
Excellent Dynasty just cannot compete
with the highly revered legend from Excellent Era.
When Excellent Era was in a tough spot,
they once tried to reach out to Ye Qiu
[Happy Cybercafe]
and ask him to assist them
as a consultant.
Unfortunately, Ye Qiu declined.
We feel sorry for his refusal.
[We Object!! The establishment of Happy!]
But we must respect Ye Qiu's decision.
God Ye, why did you start another team?
If you want to make a comeback, why not return to Excellent Era?
The team asked you to return, but you refused.
Now you've formed your own team
to compete in the challenge matches.
Are you deliberately opposing the team?
[Ye Qiu would do anything to win]
[Is it considered a betrayal to the fans
when Ye Qiu established Happy?]
[Ye Qiu and Excellent Era's
competitive rivalry]
[Ye Qiu VS Excellent Era]
[Glory League's "Excellent Era Incident:"
Ye Qiu and Excellent Era trending...]
Excellent Era is already out.
Instead of helping, you've started a new team
and caused trouble for Excellent Era.
Ye Qiu, you're not playing fair!
Reopening this new era
Reuniting with my heart's desire
Where my passion lies
My dream is still rampant
A fallen star that is still hopeful
Sparks fly, the fingers that wake up
a soul that's unafraid of the darkness
Until we carry all before it
and return to glory
Exclaiming glory,
breaking the cycle of fate
Perhaps the hardships
could make us tougher
Seeing my own reflection in the sweat
No turning back
A match with no retreats
Seize the moment
Against all odds until the end
You took away
My reason to give up
Let the wild dream revive our memories
Youth is beyond nostalgic
It's to transcend the future
Yet still striving for more