Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Happy Cybercafe]
Ye Qiu, that was not cool!
Bring God Ye back to Excellent Era!
Come out!
Where is Ye Qiu?
Give me a break.
Ye Qiu!
We want answers!
They can't get away with those lies!
I'll talk to them.
[Glory Professional Alliance Playoffs]
Based on the info we have,
Lord Grim from Team Happy
is not Ye Qiu.
Could it be an act of boosting?
If that is the case,
Stop yelling. Stop yelling.
the rule states that
Dismiss!
the character will be banned.
The League is clarifying.
Cheating players and teams
Where is it?
Let me see it.
What did they say?
will be disqualified.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Dismiss.
No way!
Everybody, wait!
A waste of my time.
Darn it.
The words came from Excellent Era.
They got themselves a scapegoat.
Excellent Era owes us an explanation.
We don't deserve to get swindled.
Let's go.
Come on.
Follow my lead!
Let's go!
We need some answers!
[Excellent Era]
Show yourselves, Excellent Era!
Excellent Era!
We want an explanation!
We won't go until we get it!
Yeah!
Show yourselves, Excellent Era!
We want the truth!
We demand answers!
What's going on here?
Show yourselves!
Come in.
Mr. Tao.
Bad news.
The media just announced
that Lord Grim wasn't Ye Qiu.
Which media outlet?
House of Gamers.
The fans are taking their sides.
They are demanding an explanation.
What about the League?
What's their response?
They have confirmed
that Ye Qiu is not among Team Happy's
registered players.
That's not possible!
He never signed up?
This is the angle we'll use to explain our claims.
He never signed up as a player,
but he must still be in Guild Happy.
Understood.
There's another matter.
[Excellent Era Youth E-sports
Training Room]
Isn't that Manager Cui from the club?
And Chen Yehui from the guild.
Why are they at the training camp?
Maybe they are here to hand-pick the players for next year.
I bet Qiu Fei is out for sure.
He used to be the rising star with the greatest potential.
We all thought he'd replace One Autumn Leaf.
But One Autumn Leaf was taken over by Sun Xiang.
He is now
in an awkward situation.
Shut it.
You wouldn't want him to hear it.
Li Rui.
You're awesome as a Battle Mage.
You're in for some luck.
You're not bad either.
May I have your attention?
If your name is called, come to the manager's office.
Li Rui.
Rui,
go for it.
Qiu Fei.
Bai Shengxian.
Manager Cui,
relax.
We'll make sure Guild Happy know their place.
Yeah.
With us on the same team,
Guild Happy is in for a fight.
Technically speaking,
the youth training camp shouldn't get involved with professional teams.
However,
this is a golden opportunity for you to learn.
Give it your best.
The club has high hopes for you.
I assure you
we have the skills to get it done.
We won't let you down.
Yeah!
Qiu Fei...
Don't worry about it.
He doesn't seem too excited.
We are joining as individuals.
Relax.
Excellent Era's reputation is safe.
Yeah.
Great.
Happy Cybercafe is setting up an arena before us
to ride the wave of our popularity.
You are doing well.
Unleash your potential.
Can you do it?
Yes!
Okay.
Go on.
Excuse me.
I am concerned about Qiu Fei.
After all,
Ye Qiu was his master.
Would he be willing
to take on Ye Qiu?
The so-called master abandoned him for Guild Happy.
He betrayed Excellent Era.
Of course Qiu Fei would hold it against him.
He would be a fool to pass on
a chance to challenge him.
Let's see what the kids are capable of.
Lately,
barely any Excellent Era fans have invited us to a match.
Of course.
All the high-level players
are either defeated by our skills
or feel too abashed to challenge us.
[Exorcist: Greetings. You're the boss.]
They won't embarrass themselves.
[How about a friendly match?]
[Sure, I'm game]
However,
[However, you're battling Soft Mist.]
I got some online invites.
See?
I got one here.
[Duel invite: Exorcist has invited you
to a duel. Accept?]
Get out of here.
You got crushed.
Let...
Let me have another match.
Later.
Qiu Fei is in the match.
Another one?
Or perhaps
this is a different player?
Fight on.
Fight on!
Do you think someone else is playing
as Exorcist?
Yeah.
What are they up to now?
No idea.
But my gut is telling me
I know the player.
You do?
Who is it?
[Defeat]
I lost.
The opponent is good.
Let me fight him.
Amazing,
Qiu Fei.
[Exorcist has defeated Soft Mist]
They aren't backing down.
[Duel, Soft Mist: Another match?]
Say yes.
Teach them a lesson.
No.
Ignore them.
Do not overdo it.
[Continue the duel with Soft Mist?]
Why are you...
Is that you, Qiu Fei?
Ye Qiu?
Is Ye Qiu playing?
A mistake in a match
doesn't really matter sometimes.
What matters is keeping a level head and adjusting yourself.
Do not ever give up.
There is a chance to retaliate.
Use a slide shove for the opening
to cut off the opponent's combo.
Did you hear?
God Ye retired.
Stop calling him that.
According to a reliable source,
he couldn't stand the shortcomings of the team
and the relentless boss.
So he simply retired.
Don't be silly.
Stop chatting during the training.
What's the big deal?
He is flustered
for not getting chosen.
After all, Ye Qiu abandoned him.
Yeah.
I can't shake the feeling
that Ye Qiu is plotting something.
I heard
he formed a team on his own.
He is determined
to go against us in the Challenge Round
and show us some color.
Excellent Era was his old employer.
He is turning against them.
No.
Disgusting.
It's definitely false rumors.
Yeah.
Captain Ye wouldn't do this.
I heard he rejected the boss' invite.
Based on the info we acquired,
Lord Grim of Guild Happy
is not Ye Qiu.
Could it be an act of boosting?
I was right after all.
I knew it.
Cursed Ye Qiu.
I never believed it.
He's stirring up trouble again.
Curse him.
Ye Qiu!
Calm down.
You've improved a lot.
Partly thanks to you.
You have my thanks.
It seems
the brat is holding a grudge against me.
What's the rush?
Darn it.
Not bad.
You got it after the second hit.
Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!
You miscounted the combo hits.
Indeed.
The combo meter
is still full.
You need to brush up on anticipations.
I know!
Don't lecture me!
[Defeat]
I almost got it.
It's been 23 minutes.
Is this...
Is this a coaching match?
Save the gameplay.
Watch it later.
All right.
Switch.
That match was too long.
Who was that kid?
I'm heading out.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm tired.
Going for a walk.
I doubt
we'll ever get this chance again.
There are problems everywhere.
There are so many flaws.
After you left,
no one was there to remind me.
Why?
You retired and ran away.
Why are you still coaching me?
That kid.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Is he frustrated after finding out
it was a coaching match?
Haven't you heard?
Captain Ye Qiu retired.
Cursed Ye Qiu.
He abandoned the team when it needed him the most.
What did he use to say?
Never giving up?
Now, he is giving up on the team.
Poor Qiu Fei.
He's always trusted that guy.
Do not lose your cool over some minor mistakes in a match.
Stop making that mistake.
Ye Qiu...
Darn it...
Ye Qiu!
Why?
Why did you...
Why did you do it?
Why are you here?
Boss is looking for you.
Let's go.
You've improved a lot.
You need to brush up on anticipations.
What's the rush?
Every character
carries
the player's spirit.
Identifying the player this way
is more accurate than observing the maneuvering habits.
Qiu Fei.
Are you all right?
Ye Qiu is acting all mysterious.
Who knows what he's up to?
He turned the match
into a coaching session.
What's his deal?
Is he taunting us?
Did he think forming a shabby team
would be enough to get under our skin?
I bet
he wants to see Excellent Era fall.
Think about yourself.
You had a bright future ahead of you,
but he high-tailed into hiding.
You're neither top-tier nor an amateur.
That's outright irresponsible.
[Copying 5 items]
He's all about glory,
[from video to Duel Recordings]
victory,
and teamwork.
But when the team faced a hard time,
he didn't care about those and left without a word.
What a hypocrite.
I bet
Ye Qiu is...
The transfer is complete.
You...
That's a load of nonsense!
You don't understand him at all!
I have been waiting
outside the door of my dream
For you to come back one day
Full of honor and love
The cold winter announces
the end of glory
Snow covers the night
Embracing pure sincerity
Turn around and leave
The dawn probably
doesn't want to come just yet
I have my own plans
I won't leave my life in others' hands
Explore the most powerful secrets
in a new world
The weak ripples will gradually
turn into huge waves, shocking the world
Onto the stage, overcome obstacles,
and fight without defeat
My heart is racing,
beyond success or failure
I will gain more than that
Get brighter and more exciting
The past and the future
carry each other
The glorious era
No one can replace
what is precious now
Everyone who leaves unwillingly
Will come back
since we last witnessed
a fight like this in an official match!