Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Contestant Info]
[Team name]
There are so many with similar names.
Oh, no.
Did we forget to sign ourselves up?
Look at this.
This one.
And this.
Have you found it yet?
Shut up.
Quiet down.
[Guild Happy, Active Players]
I found it!
Our team name doesn't stand out at all.
Don't worry, boss.
We are unique in our own ways.
Boss.
Let's take a look at Excellent Era.
[Excellent Era]
Excellent Era?
[Job, Game ID, Battle Mage - One Autumn Leaf,
Launcher - Dancing Rain,]
[Mechanic - Life Extinguisher,
Battle Mage - Battle Format,]
[Shooter - Match, Puncher - Lian Jin,
Cleric - Woven Shadow]
I haven't heard of the Mage before.
Battle Format?
Who is that?
That guy?
We'll see him in the match.
[Glory]
The exciting match
is finally about to begin.
[Excellent Era, the pro,]
All teams will compete online
[will thrash everyone.]
during the early stages.
After the preliminary rounds,
the teams with higher scores will advance to the next stage
and proceed to compete offline.
[Team Happy 0-0 Team Insomnia]
They will stand a chance
to become the champion.
Round one of Glory Challenge.
The match for Group A
is about to start.
But not all the members of Team Insomnia are online yet.
If they fail to show up on time, they will be disqualified.
Team Insomnia,
perhaps you want to remind your teammates again.
[1:30 AM, 3:30 AM, No Breakfast]
Are they coming or not?
Can we trust them?
I tried calling them,
but they didn't pick up,
nor did they text me back.
They probably pulled an all-nighter yesterday.
[Official Commentary, Host]
If that's the case,
I'll rule them as disqualified.
Or do you want to stay here until the time is up?
Perhaps we should keep waiting.
There's no point in waiting.
Let's just forget it.
I guess that's our only option.
In fact, I have a test today.
Well, that's perfect.
Don't get discouraged, guys.
We can do it again next year.
You aren't taking this seriously.
It's just a league.
A lot of teams are here for the experience.
Let's find out who we are up against next.
They're about to be here.
[Schedule: Happy vs. Everlasting]
It's not Excellent Era.
That's a good sign.
Team Everlasting?
They were professional, right?
What do we do now?
Let's see if we can borrow some Orange Equipment
from our friends and families.
Borrow?
[Loulan Slash]
Let's see if the Loulan Slash can help.
Lou,
can you lend me some equipment?
Reply
once you're online.
This...
Do you think this will work?
Let's find out more
about our opponent's strength first.
[Postmortem]
Lou,
can you lend me some equipment?
What do you need?
I want something powerful,
the best you have.
Our next match with Everlasting is going to be a tough one.
All our upcoming matches are tough.
They got a tough opponent as soon as
they went professional.
[Lord Grim]
I watched the match.
The beginning is always hard.
Everyone has been through this.
Did you go through the same thing when you first went professional?
Of course.
Were you nervous during the match too?
But, you still did great.
Perhaps because we were all rookies.
My opponent was more nervous than me.
I barely won by a hair.
Get ahold of yourself.
I'm doing the postmortem report.
No.
God Ye Qiu
is trying to comfort us.
Really?
By the way,
what equipment do you need?
Something powerful,
the best you have.
Do you want
the silver equipment we're using now?
I will gladly accept that.
How could you ask for their silver equipment so blatantly?
Impressive.
If you have any orange or purple equipment,
please share it with us too.
This...
Can we really do this?
I think
it's allowed in the competition.
Their participation in the league won't affect us anyway.
Besides, they have always looked after us.
You're right.
How much do they need?
Fine.
What jobs do you play?
It doesn't matter.
Give me everything you have.
Lord Grim will take whatever nobody wants.
Unspecialized, you have our respect.
Now, we've got the equipment.
What's up?
The cybercafe has everything.
You are not a salesman, huh?
You're looking for me?
What?
It's Team Everlasting!
Team Everlasting is on the phone.
What do I do now?
Shall we meet up with them?
How arrogant.
Let's go.
Grab our weapons.
Sure!
What are you doing?
Chen Guo and I will meet them.
Just stay here and continue with your training.
Are you sure you don't need us there?
Let us know if anything happens.
Boss.
I'm here.
Where are the rest?
You're from Team Everlasting, huh?
I guess
you are Ms. Chen.
I am He An, the leader of Team Everlasting.
I am the manager of Team Happy,
Chen Guo.
I know you.
You are the vice-captain of Team Everlasting, right?
He is the captain now.
Wait a minute.
Do you know each other?
He is...
God Ye Qiu.
I've heard a lot about you.
Let's take our seats.
What brings you here today?
God Ye Qiu.
Are you really a part of Team Happy now?
Yes.
What a bummer.
How so?
A team like this
won't put your skills to good use.
How rude!
Things are different this season.
With a great team like Excellent Era,
we won't have it easy.
Why don't we
assemble all the good players?
What do you mean?
I watched your performance a while ago.
A few of you did quite well.
I believe that you were coaching them.
But with all due respect,
I think your team roster
is rather lackluster.
And what's your suggestion?
That's why we are here today.
Team Everlasting has more resources than Team Happy.
God Ye Qiu.
Why don't you join Team Everlasting?
You can easily defeat Team Excellent Era.
Well said.
If that's the case,
why don't Team Everlasting join Team Happy instead?
Are you kidding me, God Ye?
It's just the same.
Precisely.
Join us.
God Ye,
please consider our offer.
You wouldn't want to regret this.
Actually,
I could say the same to you.
You...
You will regret your decision
one week from now.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Show yourselves out.
You will regret this.
That was what happened.
You did a great job
mocking those guys.
Your sarcasm was great.
Really?
Stop pretending.
No.
I was serious.
What?
I was serious
when I invited them to join Team Happy.
He's being a obnoxious again.
Whatever it is, we can't lose this.
Or they will sneer at us.
If we lose, then we're done for.
They can sneer at us all they want.
The online matches use a points system.
We all can score.
[Happy: Steamed Bun Invasion,]
The first solo game between Everlasting
[Everlasting: Gun of Dawn]
and Team Happy.
Steamed Bun Invasion versus Gun of Dawn.
Steamed Bun!
They are tossing the coin.
What are you doing?
Warming up.
Why do you need to warm up?
Come here now!
Then,
let's toss the coin.
Tail!
Team Everlasting, please pick a map.
[Linjiang Water Corridor]
Steamed Bun.
You're not familiar with this map.
Don't fall into the water.
Don't worry.
Stop right there!
The match begins now!
Both players are charging forward.
[Player: Wu Chen, Everlasting,]
[Gun of Dawn. Job: Launcher]
Gun of Dawn attacked first.
Steamed Bun, with his high agility, took no time to close in on him.
Gun of Dawn used the momentum to jump onto the railing.
He's jumping non-stop. How annoying.
Coward.
Come here and fight me head-on.
Why don't you
come up here?
Gun of Dawn found a vantage point.
[lv70 Gun of Dawn]
Steamed Bun Invasion
[lv70, Steamed Bun Invasion]
can't close in.
You should get into the water now.
What are you waiting for?
It's on you if we lose this match.
Steamed Bun.
Do something!
Why is this map so confusing?
I'm sorry.
[Defeat]
[Lousy]
Gun of Dawn
[He trashed him!]
won the first match!
[Now you know what a pro can do!]
[What a joke.]
We expected nothing less
[How did Happy last this long?]
from the Captain of Team Everlasting.
He won the match effortlessly.
Yifan.
You're next.
[Glory]
The second match is the Linjiang Water Corridor too.
Shoot Here, the Shooter, versus One Inch Ash, the Phantom Swordsman.
[Everlasting, Shoot Here. Job: Shooter]
Team Everlasting has planned a very specific formation.
Is this going to be a quick match too?
He dived into the water!
One Inch Ash decided to dive into the water.
It requires a lot of skills to fight underwater.
Facing Team Everlasting, who used to play professionally,
One Inch Ash was really bold to dive into the water.
He's going after him.
Shoot Here is searching for his opponent on the shore.
It's very difficult to locate his underwater opponent.
Where did he go?
I wouldn't dare go underwater.
What a nice ambush!
[Well done, Happy!]
One Inch Ash did
[Team Everlasting was giving away points.]
a nice underwater ambush.
Good job, Yifan.
Nice win.
Why are they still cursing?
Well done.
Wei Chen.
It's your turn.
Sure.
I'll teach these juniors a good lesson.
Overwhelmed!
An overwhelming defeat!
It's been a long time since we last saw this in a match.
Hah!
That's it.
Take it easy.
We have the Group Match later.
Tang, take care of the Arena Match.
Try to hold them back.
It doesn't matter that you're fighting against three of them.
I'll try my best.
[Everlasting: Furious Sky,
Job: Qigong Master]
[lv70, Furious Sky]
Nice!
[lv70, Elemental Mage. lv70: Soft Mist]
[lv70, Elemental Mage]
Another point!
Good job.
Stay composed.
Don't let your guard down.
Sure.
[Soft Mist vs Bygone]
[lv70 Soft Mist]
[Happy 4:1 Everlasting]
[Happy 4:2 Everlasting]
I did my best.
Tang Rou did a good job.
One more match.
Next,
let's find out how long he will take.
What are you doing?
Are you quitting?
The match is over.
[Happy 5:2 Everlasting]
You...
What did you do?
It's not too surprising.
I simply know the map better than they do.
We might win the solo matches,
but when it comes to Group Match,
they are a professional team after all.
Don't let your guard down.
Good luck!
Happy sucks.
Look.
They are losing it.
Come on, Everlasting!
It's embarrassing if Happy beats you!
All the best, Everlasting!
You can win this!
Happy, good job!
You're just fighting against a nobody.
That's all the Happy can do.
Trash team.
What did you say?
I said
that Happy is a trash team!
Didn't you hear me?
Good luck, Team Everlasting!
Crush them!
Happy will be the last team standing!
Everlasting will go home crying today!
Everlasting will win!
Everlasting always wins!
Did you not hear me?
Everlasting is the best!
What a joke.
They are fighting!
What are they doing?
They are crazy.
Happy barely has any fans.
Good luck, Happy!
[Dancing Rain]
The goddess is here!
Happy is the best!
How did it go?
Have you thought
about my offer?
You need a platform where you can perform.
Dang it.
Glory requires a lot of teamwork.
You don't have to do it alone.
Stop fighting.
You can't win when you're alone.
[Glory]
Think about it.
Pick a platform that suits you better.
You know where to find me.
The battle seems to get out of control
Confusing blues, struggling
in a hopeless situation in vain
Trapped in deep water
The cold rain approaches in full fury
The lonely knight waves his sword
for his dreams
There's surely a loophole
within the perimeter
Invisible mirage, shaking earth
The continuous cheer is deafening
Disappearing in a flash
There's only one result
Which is success
Who rules the world
In a blink of an eye
Advancing like there's no resistance?
Let the fingertips fly
Slashing through the sky
Riding on the wind
Breaking through
all rules and constraints
With no heavy hearts
If we're drawn to meet
at the battlefield
We'll still take it easy
Come on
Charge towards the glints of swords
Charge towards the target
And attack
Strive for success
Let's forget
About all the pain
The winner is the king
Who will emerge victorious?