Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
What are you busy with this early in the morning?
Morning, Cao.
You're awake.
For yesterday's Challenge League,
Team Happy won against Team Everlasting.
That's nothing new.
Cao.
Say, do you think we can interview Guild Happy?
[No interviews]
Judging from the news within the circle,
Ye Qiu is in Team Happy.
It should be a sure thing by now, right?
Chang.
You may go.
I have great expectations of you.
Alright.
Cao, I'll be going, then.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Be careful.
What's going on?
Sorry about that.
I...
I guess my riding skill was...
It was quite terrible.
When I got anxious, I...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sorry about that.
It's my fault for being too anxious.
I was too quick.
That's why she...
Get out of the way!
That hurts!
Ms. Chen,
sorry about that.
Why don't we
head to the hospital?
I'm fine.
What have I done?
I'm okay.
Come.
Let me introduce him to you guys.
Please have a seat.
This is a reporter from House of Gamers.
He's Chang Xian.
Hello, everyone.
You may call me Chang.
This is Tang Rou.
She's a Battle Mage player who uses Soft Mist.
Hello.
So the Soft Mist user who took on two players alone in the Challenge League
is actually a beauty?
This is Qiao Yifan.
Qiao was originally from Team Tiny Herb.
He
Hello.
joined us
after his contract expired.
What?
You mean the champion, Team Tiny Herb?
That's Wei Chen.
He's a Warlock player
who uses Wayward Formation.
He was also the ex-captain of Team Blue Rain.
Hey, boy.
Team Blue Rain?
Ex-captain?
Young man,
calm down.
Don't be surprised by the titles we possess.
This is Bao Rongxing.
We call him Bao.
Lastly,
this is our captain,
Ye Xiu.
He uses Lord Grim.
Hello.
Ye Xiu?
Excuse me.
I have a question.
Is God Ye Qiu
a member of Team Happy?
Him?
He's here
but not here at the same time.
What does that mean?
You'll know by then.
Can we talk about
the Unspecialized you're currently using?
According to what I know,
the Unspecialized you used, which is Lord Grim,
has a special silver weapon
that can freely change to various forms.
That's right.
It seems like this weapon
is made especially for Unspecialized.
Could you tell me
how you came up with this idea?
I have a friend.
He's very good at playing Glory.
After that...
After that?
He died.
Is that all?
Unspecialized is a role
that requires plenty of in-game experience.
Ye, how long have you played Glory?
I'm back.
Did you see Ye Qiu there?
No, I didn't.
Don't be anxious.
Take your time.
I'll go and organize the content I received, then.
I'll try to finish it before Monday's publication.
You have plenty of time.
Just take your time.
We will never publish your interview on Monday.
But why?
It's because the contest isn't over yet.
Don't forget.
There are two rounds to the contest.
Ultimately, victory
But...
depends on points.
Are you 100% sure
that there's no chance for Team Everlasting to make a comeback
in the second round?
[Glory]
[Glory Pro League Challenge, Solo Match]
[Steamed Bun Invasion VS Gun of Dawn]
[Concealed Light VS Elemental Mage]
[Windward Formation VS Shooter]
[Steamed Bun Invasion VS Gun of Dawn]
[Defeat]
[Concealed Light VS Elemental Mage]
You've improved a lot.
Value the opportunity to compete
and gather experience gradually.
Victory will come eventually.
It will come.
Kid, don't be scared.
I'm here.
[Steamed Bun Invasion
VS Gun of Dawn WIN!]
[Concealed Light VS Elemental Mage WIN!]
[WIN! Windward Formation VS Shooter]
[Team Happy VS Team Everlasting]
[Stalling Tactic Against "Soft Mist"]
Can Team Everlasting act faster?
Why are they sneaking around?
Dragon Breaker!
You need more practice.
[Team Happy VS Team Everlasting]
Sorry about that.
No need to apologize.
Winning and losing are part of the process.
It'll be troublesome if we have
to apologize for every loss.
I sucked.
That's why you should do better next time.
The goal of this contest
is to train all of us.
We're trying to discover our issues and flaws here.
If so, we know
what we can improve upon after this.
There's no need to feel dejected.
Discovering our flaws is a good thing.
1V3, huh?
Will you be okay?
Boss, you can do it!
Guild Happy won!
Mr. Cao.
Now, we can publish
my interview, right?
I suggest you keep it short.
Make it brief
but informative.
If so, Mr. Cao,
please check it for me.
Sure.
I'll edit it for you.
Okay.
Cao,
I'll leave this to you!
[Emerging Force in the League,
Team Happy]
What are you guys doing?
Don't you guys need to practice?
[Ex-Youth Training Camp Member]
[Recent Condition
After Joining Team Happy]
This kid
joined that team, huh?
Seems like a great choice.
Wei Chen?
He's pretty old by now.
[Emerging Force in the League]
Why did he join Team Happy as well?
[Team Happy]
[Members of Team Happy]
Why did Mr. Wei join them?
He kept in touch with Ye Qiu after his retirement.
Really?
Ye Qiu is making a comeback this time.
And he invited him.
Were they friends before this?
If I must say,
I don't think they were friends.
They were enemies instead.
[Season 2]
Ye Qiu, you shameless scum!
I think that happened.
I need to see how good Mr. Wei is right now.
He's teasing his opponent.
I guess Mr. Wei
is still the same.
Silver equipment?
He's using a silver weapon too.
Seems like his weapon is the key here.
For this casting distance,
if he used Swoksaar equipment instead,
it'll exceed 1.4 body lengths.
We've witnessed
something outstanding in this contest.
[Happy Cybercafe]
[They agreed to the deal.]
Don't feel bad about this.
Tournaments are tournaments
while business is business.
Not many people wish to buy your team.
When it comes to sincerity,
Guild Happy is definitely one of the most sincere teams.
What do you plan
to do next?
Even if you don't wish to retire from Glory,
you don't necessarily need to be a pro player.
What else can I do?
Our guild lacks members.
Starting from scratch together
feels pretty good, you know?
You should give it a thought.
Look at the team emblem.
Isn't it slanted?
How could that be?
It's fixed to the wall.
It couldn't have moved.
I guess I was seeing things.
What's your plan after this?
I haven't figured it out yet.
What about you?
If I do get a chance in the future,
I still wish to establish another team.
Will you still call it Everlasting?
Of course.
Remember
to reserve a slot for me, then.
I'm just worried
that I won't be good enough to compete by then.
Afraid not.
With your capabilities,
you can contribute to the team
in many ways.
I assume other teams have already approached you for this.
What do they want you to do?
I think it's related to the guild or something.
You should go.
It suits you.
The team that invited me
was Guild Happy.
Guild Happy, huh?
Now, they're just in the Challenge League.
Team Excellent Era is in the Challenge League too.
If they do fail to advance to the next league,
you should at least understand the continuity of their team
before making a decision.
As for the rest,
you need not mind them at all.
Alright.
I'll give it a careful thought.
I'm almost done with the team's affairs.
As for the rest,
I'll leave them to you.
Me?
Join a great team.
Work together with them and manage the team.
I have something else to attend to.
I'll make a move first.
As for you,
good luck.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Welcome to Happy Cybercafe.
Is this where
Team Happy is?
Reopening this new era
Reuniting with my heart's desire
Where my passion lies
My dream is still rampant
A fallen star that is still hopeful
Sparks fly, the fingers that wake up
a soul that's unafraid of the darkness
Until we carry all before it
and return to glory
Exclaiming glory,
breaking the cycle of fate
Perhaps the hardships
could make us tougher
Seeing my own reflection in the sweat
No turning back
A match with no retreats
Seize the moment
Against all odds until the end
You took away
My reason to give up
Let the wild dream revive our memories
Youth is beyond nostalgic
It's to transcend the future
Yet still striving for more