[Aries E-Sports Competition]
[Breaking News]
[Breaking News: Major Update for Glory!
Here Comes Level 75!]
[Official Announcement]
Major update for Glory.
[Explanation on the Postponement]
[of the 9th Glory Pro League]
Here comes Level 75.
Glory officially announces major news.
[LV 75 Max Level]
With this update,
the level cap for all online characters will be raised from LV 70 to LV 75.
[Official Announcement]
[Explanation on the Postponement]
[of the 9th Glory Pro League]
Due to that, the Glory Pro League,
including the Challenge League, will be postponed for one week.
To all the teams who were competing before this,
this update surely has a huge impact on their performances.
The impact will be even greater for some of the newer teams that lack resources.
This means that the top-tier equipment
they spent all their resources accumulating
might end up being obsolete.
Guys, there's no time to waste.
You're completing quests that are beyond your current level, huh?
You're quite bold.
What's wrong?
We'll secure the first kill and level up at the same time.
We're a weak team.
Our time is precious.
We can only gain an edge over the pros by doing so.
I'm getting my equipment now.
It's an Orange Equipment!
An Orange Weapon, no less!
That's top-tier.
It's comparable to the silver weapon of any LV 70 characters.
Concealed Light.
I'll leave the Tiger Seal to you.
What reward did you receive?
Falling Moon Piercing Cloud, huh?
That's amazing.
Tang.
You should equip that
when you're LV 75.
[Happy Cybercafe]
[Deception]
Lone Ranger, stop skiving.
Mind your DPS.
Those who did well, keep up the good work.
Those who skived, you all better watch out.
All right.
Wu Chen, you can have Crimson Baron.
All done!
Now,
only one of the three 10-men squads remains.
Let's go all out.
[Tyrannical Ambition is the first guild]
Congratulations to
[to take down the LV 75 Ten-Men Quest,]
Tyrannical Ambition
[Spirit Stronghold's Vengeful Spirit!]
on being the first guild to take down
Spirit Stronghold's Vengeful Spirit.
Desert Dust.
Immovable Rock.
The pros are awake now.
What?
They took the first kill?
Let's quit the game.
Why are all of them online?
Once the pros are here,
there's no way we can get the first kill for Five-Men Quest or Ten-Men Quest,
let alone harder quests.
Not necessarily.
Who's online?
[Huang Shaotian, Troubling Rain]
Have you guys eaten?
[Do you need anything?]
[Huang Shaotian, Troubling Rain]
I'll get to business, then.
[Scram]
What quests are you guys completing now?
[Wang Jiexi, Vaccaria]
Trying to avoid competition
and secure the first kill?
Cheh.
Who's referring to that?
I've secured many more first kills than you all.
[Xiao Shiqin, Life Extinguisher]
I'm here to seek cooperation.
Is there anyone who's up for a 20-Men Quest?
Type 1 if you're interested.
Don't be scared.
[Sincere]
I'm not up to anything.
Is there no one who's up for it?
[Wang Jiexi, Vaccaria]
1.
Are you alone? Or is your entire team coming?
The entire team.
[Happy Cybercafe]
[Chang]
Chang?
What day is today?
[Has Ye Qiu retired for one year?]
Tell everyone
to gather in the meeting room.
Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
[Excellent Era]
I invited all of you guys here
for one purpose.
As you all know,
Ye Qiu is ready to make a comeback.
I'm just afraid that he might seek revenge on us by telling the public
about the termination of his contract.
However,
[Glory Pro Player Group Chat]
we do take past ties into consideration.
[Didn't you say Ye Qiu's name wasn't]
Even if he's up to no good,
[included in Team Happy's name list?]
[Members can be changed. It's just]
we can't do the same.
[the later stages of Challenge League.]
[He can join the roster.]
we can't do the same.
Therefore, I hope you guys
won't make any comments
when you see news related to Ye Qiu.
At this moment,
there should be all kinds
[That Ye Qiu.]
of discussions
[He completed the quests at night]
[instead of sleeping.]
related to our team.
[They took everything.]
It's best that no one participates in them.
Is that all?
Don't you think you're a little paranoid?
About that...
Actually, I feel sorry for you all.
You guys have worked together for many years,
yet you don't understand Ye Qiu at all.
He's a pro player.
He's being stubborn
in order to do well in Glory
and the league.
Do you guys think he'll seek revenge
because of how you treated him?
You're wrong.
He's competing against you people
because you were lousy enough
to fall into the Challenge League.
Therefore, Mr. Cui,
you don't need to worry.
He won't use his comeback as an excuse to badmouth Excellent Era.
To him, you guys
are just among his rivals in the Challenge League.
Therefore, Mr. Cui,
if you don't wish to lose,
you should arrange for practice immediately.
There's no need to waste time here.
It's just that you guys are stronger.
That's why he's treating this
more seriously.
I'll go and practice now.
Well...
[Lord Grim]
[This lineup is scary indeed.]
[What LVs are you guys at?]
What were you guys chatting about?
It's Ye Qiu's
first retirement anniversary.
We're planning his future for him.
[Player: Lin Jingyan]
He's in the starting lineup for Tyranny.
[Tyranny, Cold Thunder, Role: Brawler]
Look at how terrifying he looks.
That looks terrifying indeed.
Chang was asking me about your comeback as well.
What did you tell him?
I...
About that,
I'm not sure either.
But Ye Qiu
will definitely come back.
He surely will.
You made it as if you were a fan who were looking forward to seeing her idol.
However,
it's impossible for me to return to the Pro League this season.
We'll have to wait until next fall.
What will you do after this?
I'll sell walkthroughs.
Walkthroughs for sale.
Does anyone want to buy walkthroughs?
Walkthroughs for LV 75 quests.
I'll teach you how to conquer them beyond your level cap
and break all kinds of records.
What's the price?
It's not expensive.
Just give me a random piece
of LV 75 Orange Equipment.
Sure.
No problem.
Do you have walkthroughs to other quests?
Give us a set.
Understood.
190 pieces of Orange Equipment?
Although the stats aren't that good,
the gap between our team and the famous one are smaller now.
I managed to achieve this in just 11 days.
It's already worth it.
Why don't you just tell us that it's Excellent Era?
I'm afraid they're stomping their feet now.
What?
You want us to ignore Ye Qiu?
We have to ignore him
from a strategic perspective.
Just take it as if you're competing with other guilds.
I'm sure you didn't log into the game.
Ye Qiu already secured all the first kills
on the same day that the new patch was introduced.
[Excellent Era Guild Report]
Their equipment
is getting better and better.
We're losing our advantage here.
If we don't strike now, I'm afraid we'll...
Call Xiao Shiqin
and Sun Xiang.
[System Announcement]
[Congratulations to Excellent Era]
[for breaking the record
of the Ten-Men Quest,]
[Underground Marketplace.
Record time: 47 Minutes 15.47 Seconds]
Ye Xiu.
Excellent Era has finally acted.
They finally responded, huh?
They actually sent out One Autumn Leaf.
I guess the entire pro team is online now.
Everyone,
we won't have much free time in the next few days.
[One week later]
[Excellent Era]
Don't fall behind.
Hurry!
Let's break the record and shock them!
[Congratulations to Guild Happy on
breaking the record of the Ten-Men Quest,]
[Yin Mountain Bandit Stronghold.
Record time: 30 Minutes 21.47 Seconds!]
[Congratulations to Excellent Era
on conquering the Ten-Men Quest,]
[Yin Mountain Bandit Stronghold.
Time: 45 Minutes 10.20 Seconds!]
You must be kidding me.
How could this be?
Could it be the signal flare from the first boss?
The signal flare from the first boss?
That's right.
I'm sure that's the segment.
Tell the guild department to send us another batch of accounts!
Hurry!
Let's do it again!
The signal flare?
You want to snipe Happy in an online game?
That's right.
Guild Happy is completing quests after quests.
Excellent Era can't just stand idly by.
This is interesting.
I'll teach them a lesson now.
Don't do it.
You shouldn't use pro players' accounts for this.
It's troublesome.
What's there to be afraid of?
It's not a major issue.
Just don't equip any silver equipment.
Guild Happy is breaking one record after another.
We have to restrain them.
I'll get to it, then.
Mr. Cui,
I don't think we need to spend this much time on the quests.
You see,
sniping Guild Happy in the online game
can be considered part of our preparations as well.
However,
once we lose,
the team members' mental state will be severely affected.
This kind of psychological impact might not be easy to eradicate
during actual competitions.
Isn't it too pessimistic for us
not to compete with him
just because we're afraid of the negative consequences?
Don't fall behind!
Quickly!
[Excellent Era conquered
the Quest Gray's]
[Underground Marketplace.
Record: 44 Minutes 07.11 Seconds]
[Congratulations to Guild Happy on
breaking the record of the Ten-Men Quest,]
[Underground Marketplace.
Record time: 41 Minutes 37.11 Seconds!]
[Excellent Era conquered
the Quest Gray's]
[Underground Marketplace.
Record: 44 Minutes 07.11 Seconds]
[Congratulations to Guild Happy on
breaking the record of the Ten-Men Quest,]
[Underground Marketplace.
Record time: 41 Minutes 37.11 Seconds!]
There's a difference of two and a half minutes.
Seems like Guild Happy gave it their all.
Everyone is...
[Excellent Era]
What are you doing here?
It's almost time to do the quests.
Didn't they notify you?
How's the progress?
You're asking that even though you know the answer.
That's right.
Don't mess around, okay?
Looks like you have a guilty conscience.
You must be stressed out.
Of course.
Our rivals are hard to deal with.
So,
what's your next plan?
You do seem like you have a major plan in mind.
No.
Actually, I agreed with what you said
during the meeting.
Everything would be much simpler
if they could see the issue from your perspective.
It's a shame
that Ye Qiu has a profound impact on Excellent Era.
It's not about his impact.
They just feel guilty.
Therefore, they wish to prove themselves with Ye Qiu's failure
to cover up their mistakes.
They're afraid of losing to Ye Qiu.
They're terrified of it.
It's because they can't get over it.
Time to practice.
You guys did great.
I'm serious.
Guild Happy is only able to achieve such records
because they spent all their time on conquering the quests.
We're doing this
to impede them
so that they won't be able
to progress that smoothly.
Therefore,
to us, conquering quests aren't that important.
What about this?
We can drop the quests for now.
What?
Are we really dropping the quests?
Yeah.
We should focus more on the competitions and training.
As for a small matter like the quests,
we can play them when we're bored
or if we have
too much free time on our hands.
Small matter?
Xiao Shiqin!
You actually called it a small matter?
I'll call you Small Matter from now on.
Small matter, huh?
Xiao Shiqin.
[A homophone of "small matter"]
[Happy Cybercafe]
Good job, guys.
All of our characters
have reached LV 75 just after a few days.
And, our guild has basically broken
all of the records.
That's our fruit of labor for the past week.
Guild Happy would've been on all ten spots of the Top Ten Records
if we had enough time on our hands.
If only I could see the faces of Excellent Era's players.
We could've obtained more rewards
had Xiao Shiqin not impeded us.
You should be content.
I'm afraid they're more unsatisfied than you.
Well,
there's one thing left to do.
What is it?
B City is going to hold Glory All-Star Game next week.
Lou Guanning invited us to spectate the match.
He asked us who would be going.
Who would be going?
I'm going.
We owe them a lot of favors after all.
We have to thank them personally.
Let's head there together.
I've been there last year.
It felt like it was more of a show than a true match.
It's no fun.
Come on.
I even bought myself a ticket there last year.
All right, then.
Anyone else?
Song Wenyi has an exam during the weekends.
He won't be able to make it.
Luo Ji said he would attend it if he was free.
I guess just us will do, then.
Treat it like a Spring Festival's visit.
A Spring Festival's visit?
Take me with you.
This is the base.
That's our match venue.
What do you think?
Let's check out the match venue first.
We have the chance to come back in the future.
You guys must show us mercy by then.
God Ye.
Let's play one match.
One of my childhood friends
found it interesting to find tough opponents for me.
Whenever I lose,
he can mock me for a long time.
The opponent he brought here is right next to this room.
God Ye,
you should play.
Teach this kid a good lesson on my behalf.
[Player: Sun Zheping, Sleepy Summer]
[Role: Berserker]
He's good.
He's actually on par with Ye Xiu.
So you can play Berserker like this?
[LV70 Loulan Slash]
[LV70 Sleepy Summer]
[Defeat]
Lou, since when you were this good?
He's top-tier indeed.
It's my win this time.
However, if we play another match,
nobody will know
who will win.
It's actually you?
What are you doing here?
I was wondering who it was.
Ye Qiu?
Sun Zheping.
He was once the top Berserker player in Glory.
Isn't he Sun Zheping, captain of Team Hundred Blossoms
who created the Bloody Blossom Scenery?
The battle seems to get out of control
Confusing blues, struggling
in a hopeless situation in vain
Trapped in deep water
The cold rain approaches in full fury
The lonely knight waves his sword
for his dreams
There's surely a loophole
within the perimeter
Invisible mirage, shaking earth
The continuous cheer is deafening
Disappearing in a flash
There's only one result
Which is success
Who rules the world
In a blink of an eye
Advancing like there's no resistance?
Let the fingertips fly
Slashing through the sky
Riding on the wind
Breaking through
all rules and constraints
With no heavy hearts
If we're drawn to meet
at the battlefield
We'll still take it easy
Come on
Charge towards the glints of swords
Charge towards the target
And attack
Strive for success
Let's forget
About all the pain
The winner is the king
Who will emerge victorious?