Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
Ye Qiu?
Sun Zheping?
Are your hands healed?
Not completely.
But at least I won against you.
You're very arrogant, aren't you?
Do you want to go for another round?
Tang,
lend me your character card.
I don't think that's necessary.
I can't believe Sun Zheping is here.
I apologize
for any oversight.
Senior, do you plan to make a comeback?
Comeback?
My hands
can no longer handle
the intensity of professional competition.
But just now...
Of course I can handle it occasionally.
But it cannot last for too long.
Did you think I was actually afraid to play against his Battle Mage?
Senior,
would you be interested in joining Team Heavenly Swords?
Didn't you hear me just now?
I can't handle the intensity of professional competition.
I heard you loud and clear.
But I also heard from you
that you could play occasionally
without any issues, right?
No team
is willing to fork out money for a player who can't play every match
and might even withdraw from the competition suddenly
due to his injury.
Your invitation
is littered with much sympathy.
I refuse to accept it.
Our team
requires the guidance of a top-tier veteran like you.
We still need you
even if you can't compete.
That's right.
I told you guys long ago.
Your team should consist of
a veteran like him.
Even if he's bad at the game,
his presence will still help the team out.
Come again?
Don't take it personally.
As a team owner who loves Glory
and was once a pro player myself,
I won't construct my team based on profits and interests alone.
I would actually send you an official invitation
if you do make a comeback.
Senior,
think about it.
Join us.
I can give it a try.
This is great!
However,
the transfer window for this season is closed.
Senior, you can only make an appearance in the next season.
I know that.
If so, why don't you join Team Happy
for the remaining season?
Team Happy?
You want me to play in the Challenge League?
You do care about Glory after all.
You even know about the Challenge League.
Listen,
you're very lucky.
We're one match away from the offline tournament.
You can make it in time
if you join us now.
And, we'll encounter Excellent Era
in the Challenge League.
You can use this chance to defeat them
and seek revenge against them for stealing the trophy from you.
God Ye, you were the one who led Team Excellent Era
when they defeated Team Hundred Blossoms.
You want me to help you seek revenge against Excellent Era?
Seek revenge?
I just want to win.
Excellent words.
Actually, I'm the same.
Sign me up.
Nice.
It's decided?
Now, we have another pro on the team.
Now, we stand a higher chance of defeating Excellent Era.
There's a drinking party at my place
after the event.
All of you should come.
Sure.
Do we have to be this formal?
I'm not used to it at all.
You're here.
You seem pretty familiar with the place.
Indeed.
We've been playing Glory here all along.
This is amazing.
It's just like what I saw in the movies.
Are there any pro players here?
No.
All of them are my friends in business.
I wish to recommend Team Happy to them.
Are we trying
to get sponsors here?
Come.
Let me introduce them to you all.
Guys, I have some friends
that I want to introduce to you all.
This is the official best player of Glory.
This is Ye Qiu, also known as
God of Glory.
He's the first and only player to win
This guy...
the Glory Professional Alliance
three times in a row.
You guys are just a bunch of gamers.
Why are you all acting as if you are major figures?
What did you say?
Why are you raising your voice?
People like you
who only play video games all day long
are clueless,
incompetent, and uneducated.
You!
I have nothing
to say to a person like you.
You're uneducated.
Of course you can't think of anything to say.
You guys can never compare
to people like me.
You mustn't say that.
Many of Glory's players are talented.
For them, gaming is just a pastime.
It's the same thing as you coming to the club
to drink and gamble.
I was referring to you,
the so-called "pro players".
Playing games is the only thing you know.
I beg
to differ.
If so, do you have any talents
that you can show us?
Maybe you can play the piano
or other instruments?
Why don't you play us a song?
If not,
you can try and hold your liquor in front of everyone here.
He's too much!
Sorry about that.
I'll skip the drinking part.
But I can perform
a song for you.
What did you say?
God Ye has kept his skills well hidden, huh?
Indeed.
Say,
since you're telling me to play the piano,
do you know how to play it yourself?
Of course.
I'll play something for you right now.
You don't need to outshine me.
It's good enough as long as you can play what I played.
Don't tell me you're planning to play random notes?
Don't you think it's meaningless
to try and be witty here?
Don't tell me he's actually playing random notes?
No.
This piece is called "The Flight of the Bumble Bee".
It's very fast.
Usually, people will play this piece to show how fast their hands are.
To show how fast their hands are, huh?
I see.
I'm sure that guy can't do it.
He's not the only one.
At this speed,
there aren't many people in the world who can perform it.
Are you serious?
My hands are stiff.
How is it?
Mind playing it again?
You...
You are just fast
at playing notes.
You don't know music at all!
How could you say so?
At most, you can only say that I didn't study much.
However,
at least I performed a piece accurately.
It's your turn.
Don't tell me you can't do it?
If so, can I say
that you're clueless,
incompetent, and uneducated?
You!
It's pointless to play something like that!
You should play real music instead!
No problem.
Tang,
do you wish to give it a try?
You were making a lot of comments just now.
I'm sure you're good at this as well.
Is she also a pro player?
No substitute is allowed!
I'm not one yet.
But I'm trying my best to become one.
Will Tang be fine?
That sounds familiar.
You chose to be a pro player
when you're this good at playing the piano?
I feel sorry for you.
Sorry for the concern, then.
Don't you think
you're letting down your family by doing so?
Thank you for showing her family
some concern as well.
Is that the chairman of Tang Group?
Is that beautiful lady his daughter?
I could tell
that it was you from the sound.
What are you doing here?
I came here with my friends.
They are Chen Guo,
Ye Xiu,
and Bao.
Hello, mister.
This is my father.
They must be the friends you're spending time with.
Hello.
You do keep your background well-hidden.
Indeed.
Thank you for looking after Rou.
Please allow me to speak with my daughter.
Sure.
Tang actually came from a wealthy background, huh?
If so, is she still able
to play video games with us in the future?
Hey!
I'm not done yet!
Don't run away.
I remember that there's a club rule
which states that we can kick someone out of the club
if more than four of the members voted for it.
Isn't that so?
That's right.
Excellent.
I suggest
kicking this clueless,
incompetent, and uneducated guy
out of the club.
Well,
mister,
please leave.
I'll remember this!
Everyone,
let's continue.
Seems like everyone on Team Heavenly Swords
is wealthy, huh?
Young Lady,
take care.
do you need me to carry your bag?
Come.
Let's go upstairs.
So,
what's going on?
Actually, it isn't as complicated as you think.
Initially, I was studying music overseas.
After that, I felt like quitting.
My father said,
"Come back if you don't feel like studying it."
I came back after that.
I passed by your cybercafe when I was taking a walk.
I saw that you guys were trying to recruit a manager.
Therefore, I joined you guys.
Well...
Is your father actually okay with this?
To my father,
it doesn't matter what I do.
He kept saying
that it's fine as long as I can live healthily and happily.
If so, that means your father knows
that you intend to be a pro player, right?
Yeah.
That means
you can still
form a team with us, right?
Of course.
Let's do it together, then!
[B City Airport]
[Happy Cybercafe]
Our biggest gain this time around
is obtaining a veteran like Sun Zheping.
After this, the Challenge Round
will be held as an offline tournament.
[Entry Details]
Most of the teams aren't scary at all.
But we need to take note of teams like Excellent Era,
Mystique,
and Deity Slayer, which are professional teams.
Next, all 20 teams
will be grouped by a random draw.
I'll attend the lot-drawing ceremony
at the League HQ.
Sure.
It's the same no matter who attends it.
Draw a good one for us.
The lot-drawing ceremony shall begin.
Firstly,
let's invite Feng Xianjun,
of Glory Professional Alliance,
to the stage.
I would like to thank all the teams
for participating in this season's Challenge Round.
Besides the familiar teams
we see often,
Xiao Shiqin?
there are plenty of new faces around too.
I'm very relieved
that we've reached Season 9 of Glory Pro Alliance.
Where's Ye Qiu?
This is a huge deal.
I'm looking forward to the vigor
How could the captain be absent?
provided by the new blood here.
Is Team Happy looking down
on the Challenge Round?
Let's hope that the
What?
The captain of Team Happy is absent.
league can grow healthily.
But the boss is here.
Let's all work together.
Let us
Why?
Are you interested in joining us?
fare better
in holding a fair
Cheh.
and positive league
Not interested.
for the game.
Next, the computer will randomly
draw the group lot for the teams.
Team representatives, please come to the stage.
Number four,
Team Happy.
Group B
I hope we won't be in the same group as the pro teams.
Especially Excellent Era.
Team Mystique.
Group B
Speak of the devil, huh?
Team Excellent Era.
Please don't join Group B.
[Group B]
[Team Happy, Team Mystique]
Group D.
This is great!
Group B.
Cloud Pavilion is unlucky.
They're out of luck now that they're facing
Luckily, I'm not in Group B.
Team Happy.
I wish to avoid pro teams.
But the other teams wish to avoid Team Happy.
This feels
pretty good.
[Happy Cybercafe]
Happy and Excellent Era are in two different groups.
They can only encounter each other
in the finals if it does happen.
Unfortunately, both Mystique
and Deity Slayer
are in the same group as us.
If we wish to enter the finals,
we have to defeat both teams.
Head home and enjoy your Spring Festival celebration.
After that,
let's get ready for the matches.