Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
You're here.
Sorry for being late.
You better be.
Follow me.
Chen.
This is Chang Xian. He's the reporter from House of Gamers, City H stop.
He's in charge of reporting Guild Happy's happenings.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Please complete your check-in at the reception.
Best of luck in your competition.
I have high hopes for you!
Here, look!
[Entry Details. Job, Unspecialized.
Game ID, Lord Grim. Player, Ye Xiu.]
I can't believe Ye Qiu is not included.
[Berserker. Sleepy Summer. Sun Zheping.]
Sun Zheping?
Why is he in their team?
Okay, whatever.
What about
Ye Qiu?
I thought he uses the assumed name of Ye Xiu
as he's concerned that if his identity is revealed, his fans will pester him.
But why is Ye Qiu still in hiding
during the competition?
I don't feel good about this.
Perhaps
he's scheming something.
Seems like
I'd need to pay him a visit in person.
Is Ye Qiu from Team Happy here?
No.
Which room
did Ye Xiu get?
Well...
Team Happy is taking room 721 to 726 on floor 7, Block A.
I'm not sure about their check-in details.
All right.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you!
League Chairman.
[Feng Xianjun, League Chairman]
Feng Xianjun.
Which side is Team Happy taking?
Block A, floor 7, room 721 to 726.
Why is the League Chairman interested in Guild Happy?
The bosses of Excellent Era went to Guild Happy's room too.
There will surely be a big scoop surrounding them.
Chang Xian.
Which room is Ye Xiu
from Guild Happy staying in?
Room 722.
Hurry over.
I'll be there in a jiffy.
Don't let the others get to it first.
Come in.
You're here, Chang.
Please continue.
Where is your team leader, Ye Xiu?
Where is he?
We'd like to meet him in person.
Ye Xiu?
Isn't that me?
You're even admitting that it's you.
Why not?
Are you nuts?
You're using a fake identity to join the competition.
Do you think that we're all blind?
Who told you that I'm using a fake identity?
This is the funniest joke I've ever heard.
If this is not a fake identity,
is Ye Qiu a fake identity, then?
Do you really think
that not many people know about you,
so you can change your identity as you please?
No one would find out, huh?
So Ye Xiu
is Ye Qiu?
Well,
am I supposed to know about this?
You're right.
Actually, Ye Qiu is my alias.
This isn't a joke.
It is
a lie.
What did you say?
I didn't
have my identity card, then.
So you made a fake ID?
Not really.
I used someone else's ID.
[Xiu. Qiu.]
If I said we're twins,
it might sound like a plot in a novel.
What?
Twins?
That's right.
I used my twin brother's identity
to join the competition.
The identity I'm using right now, Ye Xiu,
is actually my real identity.
Well...
Do you really think
that once you assume your real identity,
you can just act as if nothing happened?
Are we all fools to you?
Of course not.
Thus, we must
take this matter seriously.
We?
I was in Excellent Era, wasn't I?
I used that identity
and helped Excellent Era to secure three championships.
Are you pretending to forget about that?
If we talk this through internally,
it'd easy for us to explain to the others.
How do we explain this?
Who is it?
It's me,
Feng Xianjun.
We need to hide.
Toilet.
Underneath the bed.
Never mind.
Some things are bound to happen.
Fine.
Open the doors.
What a big crowd!
Mr. Feng.
Ye Qiu.
You're here indeed.
Close the door.
You.
But reporter Mr. Cao is arriving soon.
Quick, close the door.
Reporter?
I'm sorry, Cao.
Hold on!
Darn it!
Guild Happy
has another team member named Ye Xiu?
Have a seat too, Mr. Feng.
Let me explain to you.
Okay.
Here, Mr. Feng.
Why?
Is it complicated?
What's the matter?
You're in good health recently, right?
If so, I'll go ahead, then.
The person you've been searching for, Ye Xiu,
is actually Ye Qiu.
[Ye Xiu is Ye Qiu]
[Fake identity? Fake name?
Fake person?]
[How to prove the credibility
of the competition?]
[Shocking scandal! What happened?]
Pills.
Take your pills, Mr. Feng.
Hurry up.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
What exactly happened?
Well, the story goes like this.
What are they talking about?
Darned Chang Xian.
How ungrateful he is.
This is it.
What do your brother do for a living?
A lot of things.
Are you trying to make the best out of this
and act like he's Ye Qiu?
That would be a big problem.
Not really.
I just want to confirm
if it's always been you playing solo in the competition.
That is for sure.
How are you going to explain this?
Alias.
Change of names.
Whatever it is.
Why was I here again?
Ye Qiu is your online alias.
Your real name is Ye Xiu.
Sure.
Come on.
Mr. Tao.
Mr. Cui.
You're the one
who caused this trouble.
But in the end,
it's either Excellent Era or the League that ends up cleaning up the mess.
As the one involved, you don't need to do anything.
You're really something else.
Chang.
You can't publish the news, okay?
[Ye Xiu is Ye Qiu!]
[Ex-captain of Excellent Era used
his twin's identity to join competition?]
[Excellent Era's boss is clueless?]
Since you trust me so much,
don't you worry.
I won't tell a soul about this.
During the Challenge League application this afternoon,
the two teams, Excellent Era and Guild Happy met.
But the players of Excellent Era were shocked to discover
that the Unspecialized player with the account named Lord Grim, Ye Xiu,
is actually their former leader, Ye Qiu.
Let's listen to what Tao Xuan, the CEO of Excellent Era has to say about this.
I still can't believe that Ye Qiu has become our opponent.
He made a comeback with a new identity,
becoming Excellent Era's opponent in the Challenge League.
I have no idea either.
I just hope that Ye Qiu and Excellent Era
can stay in the perfect moment in the past.
Shameless.
Excellent Era is so shameless.
How should we deal with this?
Defeat them.
Apart from that?
Isn't that enough?
That is a must.
But as of now,
how can we retaliate?
There's no need to do so.
Stop being a coward, okay?
You're always the scapegoat.
You always take the blame like a fool.
How vulgar of you.
This isn't time for laughing.
Gosh!
Calm down.
Tomorrow is the competition.
Just leave the matter to them.
Let's not distract ourselves.
We must defeat Excellent Era.
That's a must.
Reopening this new era
Reuniting with my heart's desire
Where my passion lies
My dream is still rampant
A fallen star that is still hopeful
Sparks fly, the fingers that wake up
a soul that's unafraid of the darkness
Until we carry all before it
and return to glory
Exclaiming glory,
breaking the cycle of fate
Perhaps the hardships
could make us tougher
Seeing my own reflection in the sweat
No turning back
A match with no retreats
Seize the moment
Against all odds until the end
You took away
My reason to give up
Let the wild dream revive our memories
Youth is beyond nostalgic
It's to transcend the future
Yet still striving for more
The last team to secure a spot
in the Challenge League finals
is Team Happy!
[Finals. Team Happy.]
Their opponent
[Team Excellent Era.]
for the next round
is Excellent Era!
Come on.
Let's celebrate our victory!
The last team to proceed
to the finals has been revealed.
Guild Happy has won the semifinals.
They
will be our opponents in the finals.
Ye Xiu.
This time,
I'll defeat you fair and square.