Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
Well,
the players from both teams are now fixed.
No further amendments will be permitted from this point forward.
So
welcome back.
This is the Grand Final for the Glory Challenge Round.
On my right
is the team that has won the championship thrice,
the e-sports tycoon,
Excellent Era.
The cheers are indeed booming.
Let's welcome, the dark horse of the challenge round,
Guild Happy!
Go, fight, win, Excellent Era!
Boo, boo, Guild Happy!
Win, win, Excellent Era!
Win, win, Guild Happy!
Guild Happy!
Both teams are in position.
The finals consist of two parts, the Arena Match and the Group Match.
The team earns one point
for each surviving player.
For the Arena Match,
both teams will send five members in turns
according to the submitted list.
Guild Happy appoints
their fighter,
Tang Rou.
While Excellent Era
sends out
their Master Tactician, Xiao Shiqin.
They didn't send Sun Xiang.
Excellent Era has changed their strategy.
They think I'd be chosen, don't they?
Ye Qiu.
You're tricked.
They changed their player.
Never mind.
It doesn't matter.
Come on.
[Soft Mist]
Tang Rou is still as aggressive.
[Life Extinguisher]
Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher
is slowly approaching Soft Mist.
However, Tang Rou hasn't noticed it.
She's still controlling her character with boldness.
If the terrain is properly used,
the Mechanic could survive stealthily.
What would Xiao Shiqin do?
He's planting booby traps.
Seems like he's going to survive stealthily.
Okay.
Life Extinguisher has summoned a Mechanical Airdrop.
He's striking an attack.
[Soft Mist]
[Life Extinguisher]
Tang Rou is quick to react.
She can distinguish the sound of a drone
amidst the explosions.
Seems like the newbie
has an extraordinary talent.
Something doesn't feel right over there.
It's the booby traps Xiao Shiqin planted earlier!
She's in!
[Lv. 75 Soft Mist]
All the booby traps work.
A newbie is indeed inexperienced.
Xiao Shiqin easily
controlled the situation.
Soaring Dragon Reigns the Heavens.
Tang Rou
is very bold.
But she has succeeded.
Xiao Shiqin needs to readjust his momentum now.
Given Tang Rou's
unrepressed playing style earlier,
I believe Xiao Shiqin will avoid
What should we do?
confronting her directly.
If he fights with Tang Rou directly,
Continue with the strategic attacks.
he will gradually deplete her energy.
When can she find the chance to counterattack?
Xiao Shiqin is controlling the situation now.
Based on his experience,
it'd be hard for Tang Rou to engage in close combat.
Soft Mist has once again fallen into Life Extinguisher's booby traps.
I knew it.
The Master Tactician won't let anyone get close to him.
Seems like
we have a winner already.
[Lost]
Congratulations to Xiao Shiqin
for winning the first round of the Arena Match.
Do you know our gap now?
Who's ready to die?
How do you feel?
The Glory Challenge Round is no easy feat.
That's why it's interesting, isn't it?
Don't be disappointed.
Mo Fan.
It's your turn.
Next,
Guild Happy is sending Mo Fan.
Guild Happy lost the first round.
She didn't really hurt her opponent.
Mo Fan.
He's a scavenger.
His account is Deception.
He's not worth worrying about.
I wonder
[Lv. 75 Life Extinguisher]
if he can win the second round.
Okay.
Guild Happy's second player is in position.
The Arena Match continues.
Deception from Guild Happy.
Though he's not a professional player,
he was quite popular at the Realm of Gods.
Aside from scavenging,
which is rather controversial,
his survival skills
and observation skills
are rather surprising.
I knew it.
Xiao Shiqin's surveillance camera
was attacked when it showed up.
Though
both teams are out of each other's sight,
that few seconds earlier
are more than enough
for a professional player like Xiao Shiqin.
Xiao Shiqin has locked the location.
Seems like he's going to launch an attack.
I lost the target.
He's using a clone right away.
That's such a waste.
As long as it can hurt their health.
Nonsense.
I'm going to attack.
What?
Trying to run away?
That's interesting.
Deception attacks and then flees like a scavenger.
It's a rare sight at Glory Professional League.
When was it?
His direction
is plotted.
Did you see it?
This is known as skills.
Mo Fan can get rid of people easily online.
Why is he easily captured now?
Being besieged by several teams online
and being targeted
by the Master Tactician during a competition
are two different experiences.
Just imagine
that all your skills can be predicted.
It's like we're captured by a net.
It's so scary.
What should we do, then?
We're dealing with a professional player after all.
The Ninja Substitute technique.
That's extreme.
[Life Extinguisher]
Stop right there!
[Deception]
Deception no longer scavenges,
Oh, dear.
Is he into attacking others now?
He's suddenly aggressive.
Move aside!
He's coming close to Life Extinguisher.
Life Extinguisher has quickly reacted.
and tried to move away from him.
[Life Extinguisher, Deception]
Looking at the skills,
his free control time is stuck at an awkward position.
Can Deception seize the chance?
He's here.
Life Extinguisher predicted his move.
He managed to avoid the attack.
But Deception's attack doesn't stop here.
He just need some control.
Ninja.
Neck bind technique.
Life Extinguisher is caught.
This round, Xiao Shiqin didn't manage to escape.
Another Ninja skill.
Cicada Shell Double Slash.
Is it over?
Hold on.
Deception's landing position
was booby trapped.
Life Extinguisher increased his skills.
It's not final yet.
And Deception's ultimate move, Cicada Shell Double Slash, is used.
[Lv. 75 Life Extinguisher]
It cannot be retracted.
[Lv. 75 Deception]
The winner is determined
before the final calculation of the skills.
He did this on purpose.
He planted the booby traps
and showed his slips on purpose.
After luring his opponent closer,
he dealt the fatal blow.
He's indeed a Master Tactician.
Guild Happy has lost another member.
Let's give another round of applause to Xiao Shiqin!
Good game!
Sometimes,
it's better to save up some skills.
Okay.
All right.
It's my turn now.
All the best, Chen!
For the third round,
Guild Happy is sending Wei Chen.
He's using the account, Windward Formation.
The game begins now!
Instead of staying on defense,
Life Extinguisher is now attacking Windward Formation.
Windward Formation is not an easy opponent either.
He's using multiple skills at once.
He's likely trying to prevent Life Extinguisher from closing in.
Life Extinguisher lavishly undoes the control.
Seems like he's trying to get closer to Windward Formation at all costs.
Why do I find this strategy familiar?
Well, warlocks rely heavily on casting spells.
Intensive attacks
will affect their cast time.
He's casting the Door of Death.
He has cast his spell.
I think
the second player from Excellent Era can get ready now.
Hold on.
Life Extinguisher breaks free of the bind in advance.
Is this the ability of an All-Star player?
Normally,
the bind spell can last
until the Door of Death spell is cast.
However, Life Extinguisher's
abnormal status resistance
Wei Chen.
He has fallen into the trap.
not only helped him regain control,
but he also managed to stop the casting of the ultimate move.
Wei Chen is caught off guard too.
Since under normal circumstances, the attack will be given priority.
This round
[Lv. 75 Windward Formation]
has been a huge loss for them both.
[LV 75 Life Extinguisher]
He lost.
Windward Formation lost.
One versus three.
The Master Tactician, Xiao Shiqin
defeated three players!
Excellent Era!
Don't give up yet.
Calm down.
We still have a Group Match to fight.
Then,
[Life Extinguisher eliminates]
we can reclaim our marks.
[Windward Formation]
[and wins the match!]
And we can do it.
[Life Extinguisher: GG]
That was a good game!
Xiao Shiqin achieves GG!
Life Extinguisher's energy level
is too low for him to use another skill.
Xiao Shiqin coolly
left the competition.
[Glory Pro League Challenge Grand Final]
[Arena Match]
[Excellent Era 3:1 Guild Happy]
For the next round,
Guild Happy is sending Ye Xiu.
Qiu Fei.
Can he turn the tables around?
Don't let me down.
Okay.
Former teammates are now opponents.
[Battle Format VS Lord Grim]
The match against the junior of Excellent Era,
Qiu Fei.
Can it be seen as
Ye Qiu's conversation with his past self?
As a rising star, how would Qiu Fei
pay tribute to his senior?
[Battle Format, Lord Grim]
Let's sit back
and watch.
He's quite good.
Battle Format can keep up with Ye Xiu's momentum.
The transitions of skills are seamless.
His positioning is well thought out too.
It's textbook-perfect.
[Battle Format]
[Lord Grim]
Lord Grim is counterattacking.
[Lv. 75 Battle Format]
It's feints and consecutive attacks!
Lord Grim's Hidden Shadow Steps is invincible.
It has been 32 consecutive attacks.
Although the system failed to identify it,
he has done 32 consecutive attacks.
Ye Qiu is indeed the Glory Textbook.
God Ye Xiu.
All low-rank skills from each class
can deal significant damage
after multiple feints and consecutive attacks.
What should we do?
Calm down.
Have you heard?
God Ye has retired.
Is he Ye Qiu?
He's full of weaknesses.
He has improved greatly.
Well.
Is it a guided match?
After you left,
it's been a while since someone told me this.
Sometimes, a mistake
during the competition is not important.
That's right.
Calm down.
We should stay calm
and collect ourselves.
Don't give up.
Simply using skills will only lead to failure.
That's it!
New skills.
Qiu Fei.
You've certainly improved a lot.
This is another new skill set
after the update of the new version.
Dragon Rises from the Sea alongside Cloud Whirling Windstorm
form a mist effect.
Now, Lord Grim's view is affected.
Is this the chance for Battle Format?
What a creative idea!
Unfortunately,
a professional player's view
extends beyond their eyesight.
This is it.
All-skill Target.
This is...
Unaffected by the smoke bomb,
When the skill is not in use,
it can predict the opponent's position.
it's the most threatening one.
Only experienced player
[Lv. 75 Battle Format]
like Ye Xiu can do this.
Qiu Fei is ousted.
Excellent Era has lost another member.
Hooray!
Ye Xiu of Guild Happy
has made use of his experiences
and accurate strategy
in winning this round.
He's God Ye indeed.
Regardless of him
stopping the skills or not,
perhaps when he dealt Battle Format those feints and consecutive attacks,
the ending was set.
Lord Grim now
has 50% left for energy and power.
It might be able to win the next game.
One Autumn Leaf, the account that was owned by Ye Xiu for years
now belongs to Sun Xiang,
who is the opponent Ye Xiu has to defeat today.
I'll show you
who's the true One Autumn Leaf.
Next round,
Excellent Era is sending Sun Xiang.
This is a match between the former and current captains of Excellent Era.
Ye Xiu.
Where are you?
Stop hiding around.
Show yourself and let's have a battle.
Calm down.
Let me replenish my health.
Then,
I have nothing to worry about.
Don't forget your energy.
Please recharge it too.
I know what I am doing.
[Lv. 75 Lord Grim]
Is it fully charged now?
Enough is enough.
I don't want you to lose so badly.
Well,
same goes to you.
Save that for yourself.
Same goes to you.
Same...
[One Autumn Leaf]
This lad.
He knows the account too well.
[Lv. 75 Lord Grim]
[Lv. 75 One Autumn Leaf]
What is he trying to do?
What's the matter?
Calm down.
There must be a reason
why he's acting like this.
He's causing too much damage to himself.
Why is he confronting Sun Xiang?
How is he going to save his energy for the Group Match later?
I have faith in him.
Wei.
Look carefully.
My goodness.
No wonder.
He's
looking for trouble.
What did you notice?
It's a chance.
A chance to win.
We don't know who will win this round yet.
However, Sun Xiang
will definitely lose.
What's the matter?
You seem tired.
I'm afraid if this goes on,
you will lose eventually.
Do you think you're a non-player character?
You can only do the ultimate attack when your health is at 10%.
I won't disappoint you.
Sun Xiang is using Soaring Dragon Reigns the Heavens.
But Ye Xiu seems prepared.
Soaring Dragon Reigns the Heavens missed the target.
What?
Sun Xiang is using Ye Xiu's signature move,
Dragon Raises Its Head.
No.
This is not even Dragon Raises Its Head.
It's Dragon Turns Its Head.
What is this?
[Glory]
Why?
His health is emptied after all.
The data analysis is out.
[Match data. Lord Grim's health: 0:03%]
It states that Lord Grim still has
0.03% health.
Good grief!
Is this part of Ye Xiu's calculations as well?
He's indeed the legend of Glory League.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's cheer for such an brilliant match!
That's fantastic!
It was such an exciting match.
Why did you leave the match?
I thought you still have 0.03% left.
How can I play with that?
You have healing skills.
You can just replenish your health.
Which side are you on?
An able man is always busy.
Keep it up!
Let's earn another mark.
Then, the Group Match will be easy.
Never mind.
It's one versus three.
I'll give some chance to the others.
Sun.
Noted.
I've been waiting for this.
Shen Jian.
You're up next.
You must win the match.
Okay.
No.
For the next round,
Guild Happy is sending Sun Zheping.
Sun Zheping.
It's him.
Sun Zheping's hand is injured.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Stay tuned.
The Arena Match or Group Match.
he might be joining only one round.
Who will they send for the Group Match?
He was indeed the top Berserker.
It's surprising that Guild Happy could sign him in.
That's right.
I'm glad to see such a player joining the professional league again.
Back then, only the Puncher, Han Wenqing, was a match
for Sun Zheping.
[Lian Jin]
He can't escape now.
Congratulations to Guild Happy!
Sun Zheping.
Sleepy Summer.
It's a tie now.
Both teams has a player left.
Do you think Su Mucheng will compete today?
Of course she will.
She's an All-Star player after all.
Excellent Era dares not send her, though.
Everyone knows that she's close with Ye Qiu.
Who will be the last player from Excellent Era?
Who will compete against Sun Zheping?
I have been waiting
outside the door of my dream
For you to come back one day
Full of honor and love
The cold winter announces
the end of glory
Snow covers the night
Embracing pure sincerity
Turn around and leave
The dawn probably
doesn't want to come just yet
I have my own plans
I won't leave my life in others' hands
Explore the most powerful secrets
in a new world
The weak ripples will gradually
turn into huge waves, shocking the world
Onto the stage, overcome obstacles,
and fight without defeat
My heart is racing,
beyond success or failure
I will gain more than that
Get brighter and more exciting
The past and the future
carry each other
The glorious era
No one can replace
what is precious now
Everyone who leaves unwillingly
Will come back