Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
Congratulations to Sun Zheping,
Sleepy Summer!
[One Autumn Leaf]
Excellent Era is down another player.
The legendary team is forced to send their last member by the newbie team.
What a pity!
Will Su Mucheng join the competition?
Of course.
After all, she's an All-Star ace player.
Excellent Era dares not use her.
Everyone knows she's close with Ye Qiu.
The first half of the Arena Match in the finals is nearing its end.
Now,
the pressure is on Excellent Era's last player.
As both teams has only one player left,
this means
that this player
will determine Excellent Era's results
in the Arena Match.
Ye Xiu.
The last player from Excellent Era is Su Mucheng.
It's a well known fact
that Su Mucheng is an incredible player.
She's also God Ye's old partner.
Excellent Era sends her to guard the spot.
I guess they really trust her, then.
Wei.
Let him go.
What is Ye Xiu trying to do?
Are they going to fight?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I hope she will perform well.
I see.
Calm down, Ye.
Why is Ye Xiu agitated?
What's going on?
This jerk is trying to ruin Su Mucheng's career.
Excellent Era never thought of letting her play.
They put her in the list as she's too good.
They need to answer to the fans.
But they didn't expect us to stick around until this round
and trigger their backup plan.
Now, Excellent Era's victory is in her hands.
Her actions will be closely scrutinized.
The whole world knows that she's close with Ye Xiu.
If they believe she deliberately loses to him,
her reputation will be ruined.
Even if she loses as expected,
people will still question her.
So, Excellent Era
doesn't trust Mu at all.
For the sake of her career,
no matter how reluctant she is to play,
she has to win.
No wonder
Ye Xiu...
How is it?
Are you less upset now?
Ladies and gentlemen.
The last game of Arena Match is starting soon.
Let's hold our breath
as we await the exciting battle.
Once the game started,
Dancing Rain pulls away from Sleepy Summer.
It seems like she's looking for a lookout spot to snipe.
No.
Dancing Rain isn't hiding.
Instead, she's shooting intensely.
The advantage of Launcher is fully exploited by Su Mucheng.
Is Su Mucheng going to lose purposely in order to humiliate Excellent Era?
That's so cool!
Under the intense attack of Su Mucheng,
Sleepy Summer can't go near her.
It's the Stinger Bomb!
Is she not giving him a break?
That's fiery.
I thought she'd hesitate.
I think too much.
You won't stand a chance to approach me.
Let alone losing deliberately.
This is simply outstanding.
Sun Zheping retired due to his hand injury.
We don't know
how long he can endure this.
Impressive.
I can see you're persevering,
Su Mucheng.
However,
I have my own glory to fight for, too.
I won't give in.
I won't run away.
I'll persist
as long as I can.
This is my style.
Sleepy Summer endures the attack and approaches Dancing Rain.
Sun Zheping.
Those who doubt that she will lose deliberately
should be punished severely.
Dancing Rain is in trouble.
Sun Zheping's Sleepy Summer has withstood the attacks.
Dancing Rain is stuck.
She can't launch any attacks.
She has the chance to pull away.
Has she been influenced by Sun Zheping
and decided to play aggressively?
Great!
Let's battle face-off, then!
Why are you retreating?
Wait...
Satellite Beam.
Is this a trap?
Indeed.
I only care about charging forward.
[Lv. 75 Sleepy Summer]
Nonsense.
Goodbye,
[Victory]
Sleepy Summer.
Congratulations to Su Mucheng
for winning
I suddenly miss the days
the Arena Match for Excellent Era!
Su Mucheng! Su Mucheng!
when we could do whatever we wanted.
Su Mucheng!
The savior of Excellent Era!
Always a legend!
Su Mucheng is still in the players channel.
What's going on?
Quick,
look at the screen!
[Live chat]
[It's over between Dancing Rain and Excellent Era]
Su Mucheng...
Is it because of Ye Xiu?
I didn't expect her to cut off ties with Excellent Era this way.
It's all right now.
Leave the rest to me.
Okay.
There, there.
It's over now.
It's good that you're here.
You no longer need to put up with their nonsense.
Why is Su Mucheng sitting with Guild Happy?
What's happening?
There must be something to it.
Using such inappropriate behaviour to hurt us and our fans.
I'll ask the league to review if she violated any rules.
Leave no mercy during the Group Match.
All the best, lads!
Yes!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Next, Excellent Era and Guild Happy will move on to the Group Match.
Both teams are now seated.
The match will start soon.
Let's cheer for them with a round of applause.
Relax, everyone.
Just maintain the momentum like what we had during the training.
[Sun Xiang, One Autumn Leaf]
The match will decide the final winner.
[Xiao Shiqin, Life Extinguisher]
[Qiu Fei, Battle Format]
The match will decide the final winner.
[Shen Jian, Lian Jin]
[Zhang Jiaxing, Woven Shadow]
The match will decide the final winner.
[Ye Xiu, Lord Grim]
Will the players feel pressured?
[Tang Rou, Soft Mist]
[Bao Rongxin, Steamed Bun Invasion]
Will the players feel pressured?
[Qiao Yifan, One Inch Ash]
[An Wenyi, Little Cold Hands]
Will the players feel pressured?
Go for it, Yifan!
Wu Chen from Guild Happy?
That name sounds familiar.
I've never seen him play.
Wei Chen and Sun Zheping are old and injured respectively.
Luo Ji is too young.
Is Wu Chen Guild Happy's helpless act?
No.
I rather believe that he's God Ye's hidden card.
The Group Match starts now!
Both teams have logged into the map.
We can see
that Excellent Era has taken over the central battlefield immediately.
Their formation remains the same, which is protecting the healers.
This is the formation Xiao Shiqin typically uses
since joining Excellent Era.
On the other hand, Guild Happy is exploring the forest.
It's clear they're avoiding
a direct confrontation with Excellent Era.
Is it a scheme?
Stop being snobbish, God Ye.
That way.
In the face of our team,
no matter how good your strategy is,
Maintain the formation.
you can't do anything about it.
Don't disperse.
That's odd.
No one's there.
They've moved.
Continue the search.
Tacticians are indeed cunning.
That's right.
What's the purpose behind God Ye's arrangement?
I guess he wants to separate Excellent Era
and defeat them one by one.
Continue the search.
We're getting closer to the explosions.
At this rate,
we can catch up with him after this.
Wait a second.
Why is the sound coming from that side?
Why did the direction change?
Isn't Gun of Dawn ahead there?
It's Lord Grim!
He's an Unspecialized, and he can fire the guns.
He must be up to no good.
Don't worry.
It's better if they disperse.
Maintain the formation.
Let's charge towards our previous direction.
Why is Ye Xiu
separating his team?
In terms of equipment and speed,
[One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
Guild Happy is nothing compared to us.
[Battle Format, Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
Or are they planning to raid and attack
the healer when we let our guard down?
Remember to maintain the formation.
Don't ever get separated.
How come there's no one around?
I've calculated the speed difference.
How disgusting.
Could it be that...
Hurry up and give chase!
Hold on.
Forget it.
We won't be able to catch him.
Their team must have scattered.
He's slowing down intentionally
to make us run around for nothing.
It's only
a waste of energy if we continue going after them.
How dare they fool me!
If they move in a group, they will have to wait for the slowest member.
And that person would normally be the healer.
Once the healer is ousted,
it'd be hard to win the Group Match.
They must be concerned about this.
Hence, Xiao Shiqin won't let Excellent Era disperse.
But this is Excellent Era after all.
[Sun Xiang, One Autumn Leaf]
If he lets One Autumn Leaf go after him,
[Xiao Shiqin, Life Extinguisher]
[Qiu Fei, Battle Format]
If he lets One Autumn Leaf go after him,
[Shen Jian, Lian Jin]
[Zhang Jiaxing, Woven Shadow.]
If he lets One Autumn Leaf go after him,
[Ye Xiu, Lord Grim]
he should be able to oust him.
[Tang Rou, Soft Mist]
[Bao Rongxin, Steamed Bun Invasion]
he should be able to oust him.
[Qiao Yifan, One Inch Ash]
[An Wenyi, Little Cold Hands]
he should be able to oust him.
Looks like
Xiao is quite cautious.
Again.
[One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
Is Guild Happy
[Battle Format, Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
walking us like a dog?
There must be a trap.
The gun shot sounds near.
This round, we'll surely catch him.
Come on.
Go the opposite way.
Let's stick together.
Don't disperse.
They must have realized it now.
They are a full team.
They are going towards your direction.
Be careful.
Let's keep them busy.
Go disturb them.
Keep your distance from them.
The terrain around here is perfect for setting up ambushes.
God Ye.
Stop hiding.
What?
There's no one here.
It's that Gun of Dawn again.
He keeps attacking us from the maximum acceptable distance.
We can't attack him at all.
What a nuisance.
Everyone, come on!
Let's focus our attacks at Gun of Dawn.
I've been waiting for this moment.
We wasted too much energy
running around.
[One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
We must
[Battle Format, Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
oust this nuisance.
However,
is it Ye Xiu's order for him to expose his location himself?
[Gun of Dawn]
If he has some other agenda...
Come back!
What's the matter?
This place is suitable to set up an ambush too.
The terrain is odd.
It'd be risky for us to explore deeper.
I can hit him if I go closer.
No way.
[One Autumn Leaf]
Excellent Era is too cautious
and hesitant today.
They have caught up with him,
but why did they retreat?
Although the team formation is perfect,
if you look at the map,
Guild Happy has surrounded them.
Xiao Shiqin treats Excellent Era
like his previous weak team, Thunderclap.
Be careful.
Don't act alone.
Let's go together.
Ready.
Attack!
I...
He managed to escape again.
There's an ambush!
Everyone, go into hiding!
Why should we do so?
I can heal you.
Shouldn't we be more aggressive?
We're too passive right now.
Gosh!
[One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
I treat Excellent Era
[Battle Format, Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
like Thunderclap subconsciously.
We're Excellent Era.
Not only do we aim to be the champion,
but we must also win with style!
It's all right.
It's still not too late to adjust the strategy.
Captain Sun, Qiu Fei.
Go after him.
Wu Chen.
It's on you now.
Got it.
Guild Happy sends Wu Chen to force them to disperse.
However, Xiao Shiqin still tries to maintain the formation.
If they decide to attack,
Excellent Era could be more firm.
Why are they being so cautious?
Taking risks in spite of the dangers.
It's unlike Xiao Shiqin, who is always meticulous.
[Master Tactician Xiao Shiqin,
Sun Xiang, Qiu Fei, Zhang Jiaxing]
The breakthrough point of the Group Match
between Excellent Era and Guild Happy is here.
Xiao Shiqin?
Why?
As Xiao Shiqin hasn't fully adapted to Excellent Era yet.
As an individual player, he's indeed incredible.
But he's not used to the team yet, so he won't play aggressively.
He'll try hard to guess my thoughts.
He's the biggest breakthrough point of the Group Match.
Excellent Era is still very slow.
Guild Happy has regrouped.
Stop.
They've set up an ambush.
Stop giving chase.
What's there to hesitate about?
They're obviously bluffing.
What are you doing?
Come on!
Are you attacking or not?
Xiao Shiqin didn't
Can Excellent Era fight?
change his plan entirely.
With strong players like Sun Xiang,
they don't have to play like this.
Aren't we trying to locate their whereabouts?
We found it now.
But we dare not confront them.
I see.
They've been walking us around
just to make us upset and impatient.
You're right.
We must be more aggressive,
so we won't be led by them.
Sun Xiang, Qiu Fei.
It's on you now.
I can disperse their ambush on my own.
Dragon Breaker!
Seems like Excellent Era has identified the issue.
They've made the necessary adjustment.
One Autumn Leaf and Battle Format
are being pinned down by Lord Grim.
Guild Happy.
[Lord Grim, Battle Format, One Autumn Leaf]
Now it's four against three.
[Little Cold Hands, Gun of Dawn]
But can the number of players
[Soft Mist, Lian Jin, Life Extinguisher]
make up for the lack of skills
and characters?
Be mindful of the distance.
Pull it.
Guild Happy seems to be
up to something.
Don't worry.
Yifan.
Name your location.
I'm nearby.
I can attack anytime.
It's almost time.
Okay.
Tang Rou is the main attacker.
Yifan.
Catch the timing.
Guild Happy is raiding Excellent Era's healer.
However, Xiao Shiqin saw that coming and was prepared.
Tang Rou is launching attacks.
Is she trying
to breach Excellent Era's double defense alone?
[Life Extinguisher, Soft Mist]
[Life Extinguisher, Battle Format, Lian Jin]
[Soft Mist, One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands, Gun of Dawn]
Keep an eye on them.
Okay.
Do it, Yifan!
I've been waiting long enough for this.
[Soft Mist, One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands, Gun of Dawn]
How strange.
[Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
Why did Guild Happy
[Life Extinguisher]
end the ambush so quickly?
It doesn't seem worthwhile.
Our formation is all scattered.
We can't go after them.
Captain Sun.
Report your location.
We're right behind Ye Xiu.
How are things over there?
Wait a second.
It's a trap!
Captain Sun.
Where are you?
Just keep an eye on Lord Grim.
You three can settle the rest.
Don't underestimate our opponents.
It's always Ye Xiu's strategy
to have contingency plans.
As long as we keep attacking him,
they can't do much.
But on my side,
some Guild Happy members have fled.
What is this?
Lord Grim suddenly disappeared.
He must still be nearby.
Look for him.
He has left the place.
You fools.
Retreat.
Send me your coordinates.
I'll be right there.
[Lord Grim, Battle Format, One Autumn Leaf]
Are they back yet?
The terrain over here is too complicated.
I can't move at full speed.
I will wait no more.
Let's go to them.
Darn it.
They are luring us away indeed.
We're surrounded now.
It's never ending.
Lord Grim!
Where are you going?
Are you admitting defeat?
[Lord Grim, Soft Mist]
What a marvelous strategy!
[Steamed Bun Invasion, One Inch Ash]
[Little Cold Hands]
What a marvelous strategy!
[Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
There's no turning back now.
[Life Extinguisher]
We can only confront them face-off.
This is my first time seeing a team make full use of the terrain.
The area is full of shelters.
Captain Su and the rest might be...
I didn't expect God Ye to run away.
As the search continues,
the distance between the two teams is widening.
They've turned the tables around.
From the way of attack,
who's the resourceful team here?
What should we do?
Bulldoze our way out.
Attack firmly.
Let's oust them one by one.
Trying to escape?
Very well.
Attack the healer.
He's under control again.
Excellent Era's Cleric is in danger.
Darn it!
[Woven Shadow]
If Guild Happy intensify their attack,
Woven Shadow might be ousted.
Talk of the devil.
Guild Happy's
Phantom Formation Tactician
Great job!
is here.
Hang in there, Woven Shadow!
Hurry up!
I'll block her.
Find a spot to regain your HP.
Where are you going?
Wu Chen.
Take over.
Got it.
[Lian Jin, Woven Shadow]
Go for it, Guild Happy!
Excellent Era stands no chance of winning.
Is Sun Xiang disconnected?
He hasn't arrived yet.
Sun Xiang is too reckless.
He forgot who he's up against.
Find shelter!
Don't run in the wrong direction!
Captain Sun!
How long until you arrive?
We can't hold on any longer.
I'm here!