Starting over again, it's no big deal
Our dreams so bright,
it's illuminating the present
Our passion and intentions
remains the same from the start
Can’t wait
The journey to the top begins
with anticipation
Believe it, we can overcome
every hardship
Teamwork has become our habit
Myriad of opportunities are
gathered under one umbrella
Our skills are just impressive
See you there in this season
Whether the ending is
perfect or not, I call the shots
Just enjoy the competition
Chasing the future in my heart
I am going against the wind
Lie drunk on the battlefield
Fingertips flying
The battle is constantly changing
Take control
of the field in an instant
Confusion in the myriad changes
Victory and defeat are in my hands
I love it when it gets difficult
Be straightforward
Climb through the thorns
Light up the fire in your heart
Soon, the glory will bloom
Spread your wings and fly
No one can stop me
The King’s Avatar S3
Go, Guild Happy!
Excellent Era is completely tied down.
Is Sun Xiang disconnected or what?
Why hasn't he shown up yet?
Sun Xiang is too reckless.
Three from Excellent Era are low on HP.
He forgot whom he's up against.
In the face of Happy's siege,
Take shelter.
can One Autumn Leaf and Battle Format
Don't run around.
send aid in time?
Captain Sun,
how long until you get here?
We're losing control over here.
I'm here!
[One Autumn Leaf, Battle Format]
[Steamed Bun Invasion]
Taste my brick!
What?
Happy's DPS emerges out of nowhere.
Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly appeared
and ousted Shen Jian who's dying.
That's too aggressive from Happy.
The healer is taken down in the middle of the finals.
This means Happy is
Five against two.
That's our chance.
in an all-attacker formation now.
Hang in there.
Don't lose it.
Okay.
Woven Shadow, don't get killed.
I'm trying to control the situation.
I see.
They were luring us to the substitution spot.
But
now they have switched to an all-attacker formation.
He
[Lv. 75 Life Extinguisher, Map]
actually believes those amateurs,
who are a tier
below Thunderclap.
This man
has the courage and confidence to create miracles.
So
this is the gap between us.
I've never truly trusted you guys.
Luckily,
it's not too late.
After this game...
Qiu Fei.
Captain Sun.
It's all set.
Now, follow my command.
Shen Jian, can you make it here?
Wang Ze, are you on the way?
Our substitution point is on the other side.
He'll need time to get here.
Five DPS is no big deal.
I'll oust them one by one.
Captain Sun,
take Gun of Dawn down first.
Now, both teams have fully assembled.
We're going to witness
the first group fight
in this match.
Wu Chen.
Run.
Will this round
be a decisive one?
Wu Chen is being attacked.
Give chase!
This attack is clearly aggressive.
But he's quick to react.
[Soft Mist, Gun of Dawn]
He pulls away immediately.
[Life Extinguisher, Woven Shadow]
Soft Mist is here.
Xiao Shiqin is being tied up.
Captain Sun,
attack!
I'm busy.
Lord Grim, don't dodge!
Why?
Should I stand here for you to hit me?
Sun Xiang!
[One Autumn Leaf]
Ugh!
Coming.
One Autumn Leaf redirects to Soft Mist now.
[Lord Grim]
Team Happy's lack of healers,
[Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion]
and their HP is running out.
[One Inch Ash, Gun of Dawn]
Soft Mist's HP is critically low now.
What?
She's charging forward.
Captain Sun,
redirect to Gun of Dawn.
Tang Rou is indeed tough.
You're not going anywhere!
Move aside!
Stop pestering.
Off you go.
Zhang Jiaxing, come with me.
Okay.
Clouds Grip!
Come on, babe.
He's under control.
Turns out Soft Mist was distracting him
[Soft Mist, One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
from Lord Grim.
[Lord Grim, Woven Shadow]
Excellent Era's healer
is being controlled once again.
Save the healer!
But this time,
he falls in the hands of Ye Xiu.
We're not done yet.
He's in danger!
Soft Mist appears again.
Out of my way!
Soft Mist is truly tough.
Bao,
here you go.
Launch any skills you want.
Take this.
Tough break, indeed.
Steamed Bun Invasion holds almost all important skills.
[Woven Shadow]
The healer, Woven Shadow, is down.
Wang Ze,
where are you now?
[Match]
What...
What's going on now?
Don't just stand there.
We need help here!
Ah, new friend.
Are you alone?
One Inch Ash.
Bao,
bring him down.
Look at their position.
Wang Ze is surrounded
A bunch of useless fools.
by Steamed Bun and One Inch Ash.
Attacked by two pros.
What on earth are they doing?
He doesn't stand a chance
to launch the skills.
Gun of Dawn's long-range shooting
has almost depleted his HP.
By the look of it, Happy's
long-range shot works like a charm.
We can't wait anymore.
Hurry and attack Gun of Dawn.
Coming.
[Life Extinguisher, Battle Format]
Life Extinguisher uses a drone
[Dawn of Gun]
to block Gun of Dawn's escape route.
Battle Format is seeking an opening to attack.
Another good teamwork.
Gun of Dawn failed to dodge it.
He's being hit.
Gun of Dawn is going to lose it.
Finally, Excellent Era takes this round.
[One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher]
The situation has changed.
[Format, Lian Jin, Woven Shadow, Match]
[Lord Grim, Soft Mist]
Gun of Dawn goes offline,
[Steamed Bun Invasion, One Inch Ash]
[Little Cold Hands, Gun of Dawn]
Gun of Dawn goes offline,
[Life Extinguisher, Battle Format]
replaced by Little Cold Hands.
[Soft Mist]
Once the healer is in position,
the victory is clear.
Attack Soft Mist now.
[Lord Grim, Soft Mist,
Steamed Bun Invasion]
I'm not giving you a way out this time.
Die!
I won't allow that.
Unspecialized has Cleric's skills.
[Soft Mist]
I can restore some of your HP,
but not much.
Thank you.
That's enough for me to carry on.
I'm being controlled.
This is bad!
Let's make a combo.
Just as Battle Format breaks free from the control,
he's attacked by a second strike.
Though there was a bit of recovery earlier,
without the assistance of the healer's equipment,
Lord Grim's healing is far from enough.
Soft Mist's bar is about to hit zero.
[Soft Mist]
Life Extinguisher's drone
locks onto her
and is determined to kill her.
But Lord Grim covers her.
Stop them.
This is the final launch.
You're not getting away.
Watch out!
[Soft Mist]
Finally, Soft Mist's bar zeroes out.
Tang,
well played.
It's our turn now.
[Victorious Guild Happy]
Tang Rou is known for her recklessness,
but right now, in this match,
her bravery
claims a great opportunity for Happy.
What's this?
They're so cocky even though they've lost.
Calm down, Captain Sun.
[One Autumn Leaf]
They may outnumber us,
[Life Extinguisher, Battle Format]
[Lian Jin, Woven Shadow, Match]
They may outnumber us,
[Lord Grim]
but we suppress their health bars.
[Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion]
[One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands]
but we suppress their health bars.
[Gun of Dawn]
Keep on.
Lord Grim is my kill.
Their healer won't arrive soon,
now is our opportunity.
Bao,
[Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf]
back me up.
[Life Extinguisher,
Steamed Bun Invasion]
You jumped me, huh?
[Life Extinguisher]
Life Extinguisher is down.
Blonde-haired boy, don't you run.
Steamed Bun Invasion is too impulsive.
After all, he's fighting against One Autumn Leaf,
who has more XP and advanced equipment.
[Steamed Bun Invasion]
Why is my bar empty?
This mistake is a bad sign for Happy.
The almost full health bar of Excellent Era
has put Happy's to shame.
If the healer can't get here sooner,
tonight's victory
is determined in advance.
[Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf]
[One Inch Ash, Battle Format, Match]
Your fight is with me.
[Match, One Inch Ash]
Another Excellent Era member is down.
Gosh!
As expected.
[Match, One Inch Ash]
Battle Format brought down One Inch Ash.
Captain Sun,
I'm coming.
Go away.
Lord Grim is mine.
Dragon Rises from the Sea!
You ducked it?
Not this one.
Drat!
Why does he have so many minor skills?
Unspecialized is an interesting character.
Like I care.
Ye Xiu,
you're a dead meat!
Captain Sun,
I'll assist you anytime.
Whatever.
But
don't get in my way.
[Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf, Battle Format]
Too bad!
Lord Grim's bar is nearing empty.
[Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf, Battle Format]
Flanked by One Autumn Leaf and Battle Format,
[Little Cold Hands]
yet Happy's healer
hasn't arrived yet.
Beat him down.
Darn it!
It's cooldown.
I told you,
Unspecialized
is an interesting character.
Lord Grim has only a sliver of health left.
Yet, heavy attacks from two opponents are on cooldown.
God Ye plays to the strength of Unspecialized
to launch low-tier skills without cooldown interruption.
He's trying to buy time.
Whether Happy can turn the tables
depends on this pivotal moment.
This is the first time in Glory's history
that players advanced to the finals with the character of Unspecialized.
God Ye
has shown everyone
the charm of Unspecialized.
Qiu...
Qiu Fei!
Sorry.
[Battle Format]
You're on your own now.
This is impossible.
One Autumn Leaf is a God-level account.
I will defeat you.
[Lord Grim of Guild Happy,
One Autumn Leaf of Excellent Era]
Just die!
[Lv. 75 Lord Grim]
I told you,
Glory
isn't a one-man game.
Cleric!
Happy's Cleric arrived!
Little Cold Hands!
She has determined the game.
One Autumn Leaf
will be confronting Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands on his own.
I'd say it's a slim chance of winning.
Sun Xiang,
have you never
considered your members as partners?
We see
[One Autumn Leaf of Team Excellent Era]
that Sun Xiang exits the game.
[exits the game]
His health bar is still looking good.
Did he press the wrong button?
He admits defeat.
Congratulations to Team Happy
on securing the victory.
That means
Team Happy has earned
We won!
the qualification for next year's
professional league.
We won!
Yes, we did.
The veteran Glory player, Ye Qiu
We won!
I mean, Ye Xiu
is coming back!
This is awesome!
It's like a dream.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's take a break.
The awards ceremony will begin shortly.
Sun Xiang,
what's wrong with you?
The match wasn't over yet.
Why did you quit the game?
There's nothing I could do.
How did you know that when you haven't even tried?
If you can take one more down,
we can at least drag it into overtime.
I can't.
Glory
isn't a one-man game.
You!
Congratulations, Guild Happy.
Congratulations, champion team.
They brought us an epic game.
Let's give them
the highest praise.
[Glory Pro League Certificate]
[This is awarded to Guild Happy]
[Aries E-Sports Competition News]
After the competition,
we had an exclusive interview with Guild Happy.
We surprisingly discovered
the scandal behind Ye Qiu's retirement from Excellent Era.
It's reported
that Ye Qiu
[Ye Xiu's room]
was treated unfairly by Excellent Era.
[ during the guild's early days]
They pressured Ye Xiu with a contract,
forcing the Glory ace player to retire
and work as a part-time manager in Happy Cybercafe.
[Han Wenqing from Team Tyranny]
This is humiliating!
[Legendary Glory player, Ye Xiu,]
Excellent Era's downfall
[chose an unexpected path]
is of their own making.
[after retirement]
[Yu Wenzhou from Team Blue Rain]
Seeing the great Glory player, Ye Xiu,
end up in this state,
I believe all professional players
are deeply disappointed in Team Excellent Era.
There's no doubt
[Wang Jiexi from Team Tiny Herb]
that Ye Xiu was treated unfairly.
[Shameless Excellent Era]
Tao Xuan, apologize!
Shameless Excellent Era!
[Excellent Era]
Down with Excellent Era!
[Excellent Era Esports Auction Contract]
Welcome back,
warrior.
Illuminate the entire Glory continent
with your brilliant victory
and create new legends
with your members.
Captain Ye Xiu,
as the former captain of Excellent Era,
any comments on Excellent Era being put up for sale?
I feel heartbroken and disappointed.
But I believe Excellent Era
will have a bright future.
Do you feel heartbroken and disappointed
because of Tao Xuan, the CEO of Excellent Era?
Yes.
Some have fallen,
but Excellent Era won't.
It won't be abandoned because of someone's decision.
Because it's a spirit,
not a product.
As long as those
who care and love Excellent Era are still there,
Excellent Era
will never fall.
Well said!
Excellent Era will never fall!
That's right!
It will never fall!
Exactly!
Excellent Era will not fall!
What's Guild Happy's goal for the next season?
Do you have any specific plans?
Champion.
We will announce
some good news here.
Su Mucheng has confirmed
to join Guild Happy for the next season.
Last question.
After leaving the league for a long time,
Captain Ye Xiu,
do you have anything you'd like to say at this moment?
I'm back.
The battle seems to get out of control
Confusing blues, struggling in a hopeless situation in vain
Trapped in deep water
The cold rain approaches in full fury
The lonely knight waves his sword for his dreams
There's surely a loophole within the perimeter
Invisible mirage, shaking earth
The continuous cheer is deafening
Disappearing in a flash
There's only one result
Which is success
Who rules the world
In a blink of an eye
Advancing like there's no resistance?
Let the fingertips fly
Slashing through the sky
Riding on the wind
Breaking through all rules and constraints
With no heavy hearts
If we're drawn to meet at the battlefield
We'll still take it easy
Come on
Charge towards the glints of swords
Charge towards the target
And attack
Strive for success
Let's forget
About all the pain
The winner is the king
Who will emerge victorious?